Music
Greetings, Earthlings.
I mean, uh...
Hey, everybody. How you doing?
Saturday. Check.
Heated socks. Check.
Batteries loaded.
Hell yeah.
Coke. Prepared.
Check.
Vibes.
Hold on.
The vibes were good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I just sat on my headphones.
Like a silly goose.
Oh, no. Hopefully, I didn't break them.
Oh, no.
Ah, it's gonna be fine.
Something's definitely wrong now.
Hold on.
Yeah.
Okay. How's everybody doing?
Are you all having fun?
It's me, fake Oliver.
What's up, Oliver Horn?
You are just as real as I am.
Just a different person.
Different variety.
Don't think about it.
To me, you're the real one.
You sound excited to play. I am.
It's Saturday and I've been looking forward
to play some more Terraria.
And...
There it is.
Mmm.
Ah.
Lots of allergies and sneezing today.
Aw, man.
That sucks.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It's soon my time as well.
I have a severe case of allergies, so...
I totally feel your pain.
I haven't been hit yet, though.
It's gonna happen soon.
Oliver, try to find the secret in the menu.
Really?
What secret?
I have no clue.
Mmm.
Have you played Stardew Valley?
I played a little bit with the front of mine.
Not very much, though.
Maybe like a couple hours max.
Do you have demon allergy?
Don't we all?
Demons are not good.
You don't want demons.
Demons are bad.
What's today's plan?
Today's plan, Shu,
is to just simply play Terraria, man,
and have a great time.
Continue the adventure.
Last time, I managed to finally beat
the old man,
the skeleton.
And it's time to
progress further
and see what'll happen in this game.
I want demons.
Well, they are tempting,
but don't be tempted by the demons.
Hey, Mikey, the great. This is actually very interesting.
Never seen somebody play this game blind before.
Yeah.
Well,
I've heard that a lot.
It's the same with Minecraft.
It's not really a popular game to play blind,
but it's not really like
I'm super insistent
that I just have to play it in a certain way.
It's really simple.
I just want to play the game
the way it's, I guess, intended, so...
I see it, I buy it,
I play it, right? There's really no more to it
trying to figure out the game.
That's my approach to that.
Oliver, do you prefer apple juice or orange juice?
Both are really good, I would say.
I'm gonna sit on the fence on that one.
I have an equal love for both.
Tiny Gladiator. I love that name.
Happy to catch a stream live now.
Hi, Oliver. First-time commenter,
long-time viewer now. So happy to see this.
I love Terraria.
Hey, Tiny Gladiator. Glad to have had you.
Feel free to just lurk forever,
if that's the thing.
That's cool too, but... hey, yeah.
Just have fun, man, that's the way, indeed.
Just play the game, have fun, enjoy it.
Okay, well, tomato juice?
I don't know about that one, man.
Isn't that what goes on pizza?
Alright, um, let's see here.
Also, I'm gonna close down chat.
I'm just gonna jump in, guys, and play this game
for a long time now, well...
for a while, at least.
And... see you on the other side.
Hopefully nothing... is the audio good?
I didn't forget to unmute that.
Maybe I'll do a check-in in, like,
an hour or something.
Don't quote me on that.
Okay, see you guys on the other side.
Here we go.
Have fun!
I'm surely gonna have fun.
Look at me! I have a balloon!
And I have a skeleton mask on.
And... I think that's the...
shield of Getullu.
Let's go.
Okay, oh yeah, right, we're here now.
It always resets me to here when you start a game again.
Look how fast I am, guys.
Oh wait, no, no, no.
That's how you do it.
Okay, actually the game is a bit too loud for me.
There we go.
I always overestimate...
or underestimate...
the levels of audio in this game.
Okay, I got some new items.
I got the tentacle spike.
Never grab the pointy end.
That's good advice.
Um...
Yeah, let's quickly fill up the chests.
And then I want to go back to the old man.
Quick stack.
Actually, I may turn the music up just a bit.
It's kind of low.
Let's put it at 65.
That seems good.
Okay.
Campfire.
Why do I have two of these? That's unnecessary.
Actually, let's put one of them here.
I did take one of these before, didn't I?
There, like a good watchdog.
There we go.
And...
Oh yeah, right.
Armored obsidian skull.
I made this.
I made that.
Spaghetti!
How are you doing, Spaghetti?
Let me pet you.
Oh, I just noticed the animation of the pet.
Of the petting.
I didn't notice that before.
But it's actually there.
That's nice.
Okay.
Well, people, I'm off again.
I'm going to ride on my little highway here.
I'm so proud of this one, even though it's kind of silly.
My plan is to connect the whole world with this.
And it's not a big world, it's like from here to there, right?
The only way really now is to go down.
Maybe I'll make a railroad down as well.
Nah, that's probably too much work.
We'll have to see.
I look so silly in this with the little balloon.
I look like a little kid in a theme park or something.
Honestly, that's how I feel.
Then we have this place up here.
I do want to find more of these.
There's probably some over here.
Okay.
Look at all the mess I made here.
All in the name of trying to beat a boss.
I kind of want to remove it because it looks silly as hell.
Shoot it out of the sky.
What's this?
I discovered the meaning of defenestration.
Actually, I don't know what the meaning of that word is,
but I'm guessing it's bad.
Fenestration.
I'm not sure what that means.
I'll move this.
The old man is not even here anymore.
But he did say something about finally opening up this place.
Let's see if it's open now.
Put some torches.
What's that?
Molten Legion flag.
Actually, delete these.
What is that?
Oh, it's nothing.
You know what? I want to collect these books.
Why shouldn't I collect these books?
I want to make a library.
Oh, these are like little chests, I guess.
Also, hold on.
Ah, there's a mana potion there.
That's what that was.
I have to remember how to play this game again.
Bottles. Let me take that.
I don't want to take the chest.
Give me all this.
Oh my god, it's still closed.
Didn't he say something about opening it or something?
Let's bomb it.
Oh no.
Okay, we're fine. Never mind.
Oh yeah, it looked...
Okay.
Oh, it's dark down here. Holy shit.
Has it ever been this dark before?
I feel like this is a new level of dark.
Where do I go?
Actually, this kind of looks more breakable.
Use the bombs.
Throw it higher.
A little less high.
Oh yeah, look at that.
There we go.
Man, I could have just done this last time.
Diabolic sigil.
Here we go.
We've got enemies.
Give me all those.
You know what? Let's just leave these spanners here.
Probably they'll help me.
Actually, what is this? Angry bones.
I'm guessing that's the marching bones banner I need for this.
Whoa!
Carriage lantern.
Wait, bones!
I need this.
There's a... hold on.
There's a bunch of recipes that require bones.
Yeah, dude.
Maybe I should zoom out a bit.
Nah. Zoom in like that, that's fine.
Whoop!
Okay, those things just... oh, what's that? A sorcerer?
Oh, what's that?
The dodging skills.
Where did that even come from?
Give me that.
Whoops.
This does not look good.
Spike.
Huh.
It doesn't say material.
Oh, wait, does this hurt?
Probably hurts to fall into this.
Do I have sticky things?
I have scarab arms.
I want to destroy the spikes.
That's too much work.
Thank you.
Oh, look at that!
Uh-oh.
What is that?
Where does it come from?
Oh, wait!
The one time.
I'm going back.
I have a key that I'm pretty sure is going to work there.
Now the question is where the fuck is it?
Ah, it's right here. Perfect.
Let's also do this.
And you know what? Let me put some stuff in here while I'm here.
Increase movement speed.
What do I have right now?
I have this one.
Maybe I don't want this.
Violent bone glove.
Hmm.
Man, this is a nice fucking item right there.
This one is also nice.
This one, I'm not so sure about.
Maybe I want this instead for now.
I'll carry this with me in case I need it for something.
Construction.
Put this in here.
This will be sold.
Oh yeah, right, this one.
I got to have that ready in case I need to do a lot of digging.
Oh, this one can go in here because I don't want this right now.
The bones!
Hold on while we're here.
Dale N.
Tell me about the bones.
Oh, oh wait, this was it!
Bones.
Jungle spores.
Wait, shadow scale?
Tissue sample. Okay.
Tissue sample I have.
Jungle spores, I feel like should be easy to get, right?
It's just going to the jungle somewhere and mining something, I guess?
At least that's what that sounds like to me.
The banner can also stay.
Put that in there.
And the mana potion is also kind of...
I don't know about the mana potion, man.
Strong meter, hammax.
Oh yeah, right, hold on.
Yeah, I want to carry this with me.
Let me put that here. Let me actually do this.
And that as well.
Lock potion?
Oh wait, speaking of potions.
If I'm going exploring, let's see what I have.
Let's take one of these.
And...
Maybe...
What is Grand Immunity to...
So, Grand Immunity to lava.
Let me take one of those in case I encounter lava.
We have 27 healing potions, that should be fine for now.
Show us the location of enemies.
Decrease enemy spawn rate.
Strange brew.
Okay.
This is good. I think we're ready.
Let me just quickly take a look around the place here.
Dante...
Is he... Wait, sparkle?
Who are you?
This is like an amazing time to fling confetti everywhere.
Is it?
Wow, there's so many people here.
I hate that it's not for a party.
I think Seymour the Merchant is a killjoy at parties.
Wait, is this the party girl?
Confetti?
Wait, this is a material.
Fireworks.
Party center.
27 gold?
Silly balloon machine.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
Sparkle. Are you actually living here?
Oh yeah, you are. You took over Rosalva's place.
Actually kind of cool that the people are living here.
It's like a little community.
It's nice.
Dylan, tell me quickly about the confetti.
Flask of party.
Million whip attacks cost confetti to appear?
Party bullets.
Explosions of confetti on impact.
That's a good ammo.
Oh, it needs an empty bullet.
I don't know how to make that.
Anyway, let's go back.
I'm excited.
Look, there she is.
I made her a super nice house in between these two trees.
Actually, I'm really proud of that house.
It's really nice looking.
I want to do more like this for the other people, depending on their happiness needs.
And wait, we're not here yet.
I forgot to sell these.
Actually, you know what?
This one is not really that needed right now because
we're not doing much movement at the moment.
We're just exploring slowly.
Get off.
Yeah, that's good.
You, get lasered.
There's just potions here.
I don't want that.
Let me have books.
I'm actually taking all these books.
I'm going to have the sickest library.
And this just gets straight down.
Look at this.
What even is this place?
It was back and forth a lot.
Let me place this down here.
Whoa, whoops.
There, just hang it there. Why not?
A little closer. Let's see if it works.
Oh, wait. Do I have to do this?
Wait.
Am I not close enough?
Maybe I have the wrong key.
Maybe there's a different key.
Why can't I open that?
Wait, I just got it.
Oh, come on. It's got to be that one.
Whoops. Yeah, I take damage from standing on that.
I see that now. Let me actually get rid of it.
Are you shooting things at me, sir?
I can shoot too.
Ooh, you heard that?
Wait, I can't remove this.
Ouch.
Let's just free this right now.
Why can't I...
I don't know if I'm...
I don't think I have the right key.
Let's keep this in mind. There's a chest here.
Dude, I'm already excited just to be shooting this gun again.
Oh.
Look at this. There's another chest here.
Oh, this needs a icy key or something.
Okay, so hold on. I think I understand. Wait, what's this?
Clothier voodoo doll.
You are a terrible person.
I can equip it.
Hold on. What changed?
My hands.
Oh, because I don't have the glove on, of course.
Let me keep this on for now.
Maybe it'll... maybe it has some effect that is not explained.
Actually, I don't want that. Just delete it.
These guys just keep spawning, huh?
That's fine with me. There's no match for my prowess.
Combat ability.
Oh!
Oh, no. Okay, so that shit breaks.
Oh, no.
Okay, this is a little tricky.
Like I got Shad on.
Cursed Skull.
Whoop! I don't know what just happened there.
There we go. That's how we do it.
I gotta be careful with that.
Like some loose stone here.
Mining potion. Not bad.
What's that? What's damaging me?
You are...
Wait, I can't shoot.
I'm cursed!
Oh, interesting.
I guess that's the skull that did that.
Oh, my God. Okay, I'm slowly getting my ass kicked here.
I need to be careful.
What is damaging? Oh, it's this!
There's a trap!
I get it now.
Let me actually quickly chillax for a moment here.
We're gonna chill.
And Fettie can go away.
Why are we regenerating so slowly?
What's happening? Why is it so slow?
Oh, I should have brought a potion of...
Regeneration.
Don't you fucking shoot things at me?
This is all gonna break, by the way, so...
Oh, wow.
Okay, um...
What do we got?
We got a little platform down there.
I can make it.
Oh, the skills!
That was awesome.
What is that?
I kind of want to take it.
Oh, there's spikes down there as well.
Oof.
Get rid of it all.
Oh, here we go!
Oops.
Menacing Copal Shield.
Cool.
Opens all Shadow Chests and Obsidian Lockboxes.
Hell yeah.
Feather Fall Potion.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, God. We've got enemies.
What are you gonna do?
What are you gonna do? Leave me alone.
Oh, God.
And a gold coin.
Gracias.
Give me that.
Oh, another one.
A forceful... Oh, my God. Look at all these items we're getting!
Forceful Aqua Scepter.
Oh, hold on.
I can't focus on this with all the enemies.
There we go.
Use a space shower of water.
Okay, I will take that.
Someone's Eye of Cthulhu.
Very nice.
Gravitation Telepo... What is teleportation?
What?
Teleport you to a random location?
Bro.
What?
I gotta try that.
Hold on a sec.
Get rid of all these spikes.
Are you gonna come up here?
God damn it.
Okay, he's gone. Heal.
Man, I hate that I sometimes accidentally use the dash forward ability.
Because I double click on accident.
I want this.
Is that catacombs?
Oh, it's just a picture frame.
Okay, you know what?
Wow, look at the map here.
Why does it look like that?
It's all spiky and shit.
Also, there's little areas off to the sides here, too.
Um, you know what?
Fuck it.
I'm gonna try this.
It actually just teleport you to a random location.
That's fucking amazing.
What a fun little ability.
I like it.
That's cool.
Jungle spores!
Yes! It's what I need!
Heck yeah, dude!
The game read my mind.
Gimme jungle spores.
Oh, we got spiderwebs.
Where even am I right now?
I am below...
the jungle, I guess.
Which makes sense.
Uh, that was a beast!
Oh god.
Oh, I need light. I can't see anything.
Oh my god, what is that?
Oh, oh, look!
Hornet!
Oh!
What is hitting me?
What's that?
Kill this fucking thing.
Dude, I'm in such a good mood today, man.
I'm just excited to be playing this.
Exploring things.
Okay, let me dodge that.
Look at me sniping long distance here.
I love this weapon!
A spiked jungle slime!
That's nasty.
You are a nasty enemy.
Look at me.
What have we got up here?
Shoot that guy down.
Can I get that?
New music as well.
Take care of these nasties.
Okay, they actually do a significant amount of damage.
What?
Just random gold?
Don't shoot things at me.
I need to fix my inventory.
You know what, let's delete this.
Where's my thingy there?
Honestly, let's just do this.
That one, this one.
Pause it all.
Right?
Wait, what is this weak water bolt?
Also, let me try this.
Really?
Spray's water.
It's like a super soaker.
Oh, cool!
It bounces!
Oh, that's actually pretty cool!
You can sort of go around corners with that.
It does a decent amount of damage as well.
Not bad.
Pretty cool design on that.
What else did I get?
Oh, there's also this one.
Grants immunity to knockback.
You know what, maybe I'll have that.
I can't do any more of these, unfortunately.
Shadow key.
I kind of want to connect up here first and then go down.
So let's go up again.
Looks a little silly.
Actually, let's use the scarab bomb.
Wait, did I leave that in the...
The scarab bomb buff?
Actually, I want this here.
The scepter I also want to try a bit more with, but...
Not right now.
Let's do that.
Okay, I take damage from it if I'm too close.
That's good to know.
I need more jungle spores.
Hups!
Grubby!
Oh, don't break... Oh, no.
That's a lot of damage I just did there.
What am I taking damage from?
Oh, I was poisoned.
You know what, let's use the...
Didn't I have a potion of mining?
Drink it!
Wait, I also had an item...
of mining.
One of the stacks!
Oh!
Whoa!
Yo, that's totally awesome!
Jesus!
That's insanity.
Let me go up here.
Yeah, destroyed because I hate it.
Give me all this.
I have to hurry while this effect lasts.
I can destroy everything!
Oh, my God!
This is insane!
I love it!
Oh, we've got a railway!
Let me just do that.
Ah, crap.
That works.
I destroyed the railway.
Let me actually rebuild that.
Buddy!
Oh, it's a bat!
Oh, these are annoying to hit.
I got to use my melee weapon for that.
Oh, look at this little tunnel!
Haha, this is so insane!
So cool!
This is just awesome!
So that leads somewhere else.
Let me go back down here now that I connected it.
Fuck off!
Oh, man. Cheers, everybody!
Hope you're having a great Saturday.
What's up here?
Get rid of it all.
Please die.
There we go.
Loot!
And rope.
Hahaha!
Reminds me of the brrrr from Minecraft now.
That's what I think of.
There we go.
That's a boomerang statue.
It is. Delete it.
Let's take a joyride.
Through these caverns.
Oh, look at this!
Thank you.
What's up here?
Nothing.
Whoa, why is it all green?
Oh, it's just a background, never mind.
That looked funny for a second.
Man, I love this weapon!
Oh, frog. Let me catch that.
Why is it go there? Don't go there.
Yeah, come here.
Hey!
And you.
Why do you go there? Stop that.
Oh, wait, I've been here.
I went down here before. Okay, I see.
It's connecting.
It's all connecting.
What do I see?
Nothing interesting.
Just a damage from that.
Uh-oh.
Come here.
Ah!
Ah, whatever.
Release the bees!
Man, I'm actually running out of torches.
How do I make them again?
Ah, torches.
Shit, I don't know.
Probably need wood.
I don't have that right now.
Crap.
Yeah, I kind of need wood.
Hold on a second.
There's wood right up here.
Here we are.
Whoops.
So fast.
Mahogany.
Torch.
I make a jungle? You know what? Let's try that.
Make a jungle campfire.
Life regen is increased.
Wait.
Quick trash stack and ceiling will be...
Oh, right. Okay.
The little enemies are hard to hit with this weapon.
That's like the downside.
Okay.
Torch.
Do I actually need a workbench for this?
I don't remember.
Ah, tiki torch.
Any wood.
Ah, man.
Wait, that's not a real torch.
Wait, poison dart?
Huh.
Oh, there.
Oh my god.
Oh, you need gel and wood. Okay.
Let me just grab some.
It's so fast with his axe right here.
Pineapple.
I wonder if the mining buff also works on
chopping trees.
Yeah, eat the pineapple.
Do-do-do-do.
Yeah, we're good.
Definitely.
That's what I needed.
All right, let's keep moving.
Dude, I want more of those
teleportation potions that just teleport you randomly.
That's such a cool little thing.
Really neat.
What's that?
You got something.
Thank you.
I want more jungle spores.
Where did I get that?
What did I destroy to get it?
It's the question here.
Don't do that.
Is it these things?
Oh, god.
I need to heal.
I'm going a little fast here.
Probably not a good idea.
Gotta play it a little safe.
It's a bad habit.
Man, I want something that will increase
the range on my pickaxe.
Green mushroom.
Spelunker potion. What was that again?
Yes.
Okay, okay, okay.
Wait, what is this down here?
There's some kind of structure there.
Ooh.
Loot.
Let me see if I can find my way in there.
Actually, maybe this will work.
Okay.
How do I get down there?
Here?
Is this interesting?
Oh, that was a snail, never mind.
Ooh, we're in some kind of temple now.
These are the Watcher's statue.
Crawl that.
Is that a...
workbench?
Ooh, is this exciting?
Oh, this needs something to get in.
Whoa, 800?
Ah, bro.
Solar tablet fragment.
Is that what I need?
It's not. Why is this crossed over?
Oh, it's because I can't heal.
Let's put this back down.
Solar tablet fragment.
This thing just spawned it. I wanted to spawn more.
Maybe I need... Oh, there's also something here.
Thanks.
Okay.
Are you gonna spawn again?
So I can't mine any of this.
I need some kind of thing to get in.
I think I can show this to...
I was about to say Devin, but that's not true.
Dylan. And what is...
Some kind of treasure there.
You know what? Let's head back.
I need to show Dylan some things.
Okay.
Stinger.
Flask of poison.
Oh, that's cool.
Poison dart.
Blade of grass?
Thorn chakram.
Wait, these are all weapons.
Jungle shirt.
Oh.
Abomination.
Honestly, I should try to make every set because the set bonus is not revealed until you have it on.
Just to experiment.
If I hadn't discovered this,
this gun that I'm using right now wouldn't be half as good.
As it is.
Okay.
Show me something about...
This one.
Obsidian shield.
Knockback and...
Yo!
We need the Tinkerer's workshop for that. I could do this.
Knockback and fire blocks?
I guess that could be cool.
And then we also have...
What was the thing I wanted to show?
This one.
Solar tablet. Summons the eclipse.
What?
That sounds intriguing.
Can I use any other things?
What about this?
I think I checked this once.
Let's see here.
Garland.
Whoa!
Hello?
I can craft them myself.
Gold ore.
Wait, gold ore?
Moondlow.
Dude, I need to get some...
I need to get the farming shit under control here.
I need to get this shit going.
Holy crap.
This one is...
Platinum ore.
I can actually make this right now.
Right? Right when I'm standing even.
Wait, I guess I need one more material that I don't have on me right now.
The jungle torch? Probably...
Yeah, okay. The jungle torch can be deleted.
Where'd it go?
Vine.
Wait.
That just fucking occurred to me.
This is an axe and a hammer.
I didn't even realize this when I made it.
That just occurred to me.
This is a...
an axe with 150% axe power.
That's kind of insane.
Jungle pants?
Increased magic critical strike chance.
That sounds pretty cool too.
I need vines and jungle spores for that.
Hold on a second. Wasn't there an item that gave me some kind of vine power?
Allows the collection of vine rope from vines.
No. Okay, never mind.
Well, I was right that I had something with vines, but it's not quite what I was looking for.
Dilan?
What can I do with my Dylan?
Alright, that's boring.
Give me knowledge on...
jungle grass seeds.
Green thread.
Requires a loom. Okay.
This torch should go there.
The frog.
Sauteed frog legs.
Frogle bunwitch has a bigot of kick to it.
Yeah, I'll make that.
I'll make that right now.
I'm gonna be eating that bunwitch in the caverns.
Okay, I'm gonna combine these two.
Before I forget.
So now...
Obsidian shield.
Yoink.
Put that there. Actually, don't put it yet.
Like that.
Keep it for now.
This one...
I don't know.
Let me sell some things.
No, actually, cobweb is something I can use.
The rope, though. I don't need that.
I don't need the stone right now.
What else?
Okay, you know what? Let's actually get this farming shit under control
because I want the ability to make all the potions that I could ever want.
And something's not right here.
Or maybe it is right. Never mind.
It just looked like it was dead.
Oh, that's water leaf. I thought one of them was alive.
The other one was dead, but this is actually fine.
Why am I not getting seeds from it, though?
Blink root.
What is this?
Oh, this is just decorative.
Yeah, look, they just grow like that.
So this is a blink root.
Planter, I think.
Let me see what I have.
Sort things.
Blink root. Is this? Yeah.
And the other one was death weed.
But I don't have death weed seeds.
That's the thing.
What's this? A bunch of blink root?
Wait, I have crimson seeds.
Maybe that's what that is, actually.
Hold on.
Wait, really?
Oh, okay.
I could have almost sworn that would be the one.
Where did I put the...
Man, where's the seeds? Did I not take them?
Oh, there they are.
So right now, quick test.
If I were to destroy this right now, I can't get the seed bag, right?
No, it's just gone.
So I have to wait until it's grown and then I pick it and then I get the whole thing back.
Beautiful.
At least that's confirmed.
I need to make more of these.
And I need to make some for the other types of things as well.
In fact, can I just...
Can I just plant them anywhere?
No. It needs to be a specialized planter for that.
Okay.
Vine. Also, I have this one.
Deathweed seeds. Yay!
Quick stack.
Very nice. Let's plant those.
I'm not even sure what the deathweeds are used for.
But let's just plant them.
Get rid of that.
Okay. It's starting to look like something.
We need a third row of chests up here as well.
Here I want to...
Take all.
And then do this.
Do this.
Let's have a little painting.
The painting can be here.
And kind of a depressing painting.
That's okay though.
Violent bone glove.
The spike.
I want to sell those.
Actually, wait up.
Maybe I can use that to my advantage.
Do enemies take damage on this?
Is the question.
If I can push back enemies into spikes.
Think about that.
If I have a weapon with a huge knockback,
I could set a trap.
You.
Buy that.
What is this?
Clothier...
Clothier voodoo doll.
What is the point of this?
What was I able to make with the live crystal again?
Dylan, you have to remind me.
This.
You know what? Let's make that.
I need to carry one of these around anyway.
Give me chain.
I'm actually almost out of chains.
Should make some more.
Oh wait, I can probably make it now.
Tell me, did I need more than two chains?
Fuck.
Ah, I needed four.
And chains, I believe, is made with lead.
I think.
Or any bar.
Let's try that.
Dylan, remind me here.
Chain.
Yep.
Any iron bar. Perfect.
Anvil.
Let's just make a bunch.
150.
Now we always have chains.
And then, make this.
Carry that around.
Take one of these campfires.
Put them here.
Very good.
Do that.
Put the lead back.
Wait, did I have all the crimson seeds right?
Maybe, you know what, this one should be seeds only.
This one is non-seeds.
Sword.
Let me see here.
The crimson, what is that doing there?
What kind of seeds, also that one.
What is it doing there?
Seeds.
There's the seeds.
Sword.
Take the non-seeds.
Feather.
That's not supposed to be there, I think.
Oh, no more room, that's fine.
Oh, jungle spores.
And that's what I needed to ask Dylan about.
Jungle spores.
Silverthorn seeds.
All the seeds going here.
Looks about right.
Vine in here.
I think these torches here are, like, weird.
Maybe I don't want them.
Yeah, I need more chests.
God damn.
Definitely.
This is a mess.
And bone!
What else did I need the bone for?
Let's see here.
Summon Skeletron Prime.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
Bone bit.
Workbench. These are different chests.
Titan potion.
Uh-huh.
Oh, it's a fertilizer.
Teapot?
Oh!
Increased range of damage on that.
Cool.
The Void Vault.
Shadow Scale.
Or tissue sample.
Let's try the jungle spores.
Where'd it go?
Bro, I can't.
Oh, it's here.
Right click.
Crafting and then click on this.
Let's see.
Yeah, okay.
The jungle hat.
I mean, this is actually...
Wait, axe of regrowth.
Aren't these the same?
They're the same.
Ivy whip.
A whip, huh?
Vine and jungle spores. Actually, I can make that.
When I have the vine and jungle spores.
Alright, let's sort the chests.
And head out again.
Fishing.
Actually, wait a minute.
We had some fishing stuff in here, didn't we?
Bait.
Sort.
Any other...
What's that? Grasshopper?
Man, they're not being sorted by bait.
That's a bit annoying.
Okay. Fishing.
Quick stack.
There we go.
Okay. Michelinius.
In here goes all kinds of things.
Stinger? I think that's organic.
I guess so is that.
But whatever.
In fact, I'm going to bring
this one with me now instead.
Suspicious looking.
I can go in here.
Chain.
Inventory management.
Man.
Put these in here for now.
This I'll keep.
This one I'm not sure of. Let's put this in the accessories.
Violent bone glove.
Keep it.
The rest seems about right.
Yeah.
Maybe I don't want the glow stick right now.
Put it in Michelinius.
The bones.
And then we have spores and stingers.
I think we're fine.
Now.
I think I'm going to head back to
to the west.
I want to keep exploring there.
Especially because I have a key on me
and there's chests down there that I want to loot.
This effect here where the things are sprouting out.
It looks very suspicious to me.
Like this.
I just killed something.
Roadkill.
So it looks like there's an area off to the side here.
Something here and here.
Definitely want to check all of that.
I like when it rains in this game.
I don't know why. It makes me happy.
Okay.
Off we go.
Let me instead of having this,
let's put on this now.
Also this one.
Actually that one too.
So many of these things.
We're going to eat that.
Fuck off.
150th face monster.
That's quite a lot.
What did that say? Goblin...
Scout.
Huh.
They don't even look evil.
When you look at them, they look like
adventurers. Why am I killing them?
Why are they wanting to kill me?
Why can't we be friends?
Okay, hold on. It looks like there's something.
Oh boy, I can't dig through this.
Never mind.
I'm an idiot.
Yeah.
Of course.
I can't open this yet.
What is that?
Blazing wheel.
I wonder if this guy summoned it.
What a weird thing.
Oh my god, he's up there.
That's so frustrating. Oh no.
That was terrible.
Let's just keep going down.
This is dangerous.
We're in danger territory.
Mining. Oh nice.
I'm ready to perform sick mining maneuvers
later on again now.
We've got some crimtane.
We can remove this.
Maybe I should look for that actually.
Like for example here.
Maybe there's like hidden paths.
I need to pay attention to this.
Hold on.
Like right...
No, this is...
Try to understand these spikes on the map here.
It's very interesting to me how that looks like that.
Like what's up with it?
Like look, there's something in there.
I see a...
Blink root.
I don't think I can actually deal with that.
Water bolt.
Oh, is that how I got the book?
I just... it randomly dropped from one of these books.
I'm so glad I'm taking these now.
Oh, a bookcase. Oh, I want that.
Gothic bookcase.
I'm gonna do some...
housing.
Remove these damn spikes.
Make me unhappy. Get off.
You.
How dare you exist.
I'm actually gonna remove this.
I don't trust myself.
There we go.
Bound mechanic!
Thanks!
It was just a matter of time
before I ended up like the rest of the skeletons down here.
Bro, we're getting killed!
No.
Why are you fucking kidding me?
How did you survive this long?
Until now, huh?
What is it with people in this world, man?
They have no survival skills.
Heal.
Hopefully she's just gonna spawn like the other guy.
And everything's fine.
Metal shelf? I don't want that.
Yeah, I unlocked it!
That's way better than the one I have!
A superior blue moon!
Well, dodge that like a pro.
Shadow key...
Hold on, let me deal with this guy.
Jester's arrow.
Throwing knives.
Give me danger sense.
Recall sure.
Remove that.
Remove this as well, honestly.
Let me try this.
Whoa, the range!
Oh, you take consistent damage
when you stand in it.
It's not a one-time thing.
Like when you just run into it.
Yep, nice crit there.
Get rid of all this.
Fuck off.
Actually, give me that HP.
You are annoying me!
Can't you see I'm trying to remove the dangers of this land?
This is a bit precarious.
Oh, nice.
Dude, this place is cool.
I'm liking this place.
Oh! I'm trying to be pro there.
Didn't quite work out.
Can you please remove the thing I'm telling you to?
Thanks.
Oh, man. I'm taking way too much damage.
You.
Oh, I can destroy their protectiles.
Shoot.
Hey, huh?
That's awesome.
Whoops. Oh, no. See, I didn't mean to do that just now.
Keybinds are messing with me.
Oh, what is that?
It's a trap!
Spike ball on a rope.
These blazing wheels are something else, aren't they?
Did I miss anything in here?
I need a key. Okay.
Also, look at these skeletons bound.
Wall skeleton.
Is that decoration?
Hahaha.
Yo.
I don't know about that, dude.
Delete this.
See that down there looks scary AF.
So here's my plan.
I'm going to bomb them.
Oops.
Hey!
Oh, here. Oh, my God. Check this out.
Oh, whoa. There's more blazing wheels.
Hey, guys.
You having fun yet?
Hey, that's how you do it, bitch.
Pro skills.
Remove all the danger.
Get out of here.
Okay.
Let me just scratch my nose real bad.
There we go.
Can I remove this thing?
Oops.
Can I shoot the trap away, I wonder?
I'm trying to hit it.
No, it doesn't look like it.
It needs to be avoided.
Hold on. There's a bunch of enemies.
Oh, God.
The wheels.
Go.
Oh, wait. Here we go.
Nice.
Plink away.
What is that sound?
There we go.
So far, so good.
This is some real dangerous shit.
Let me tell you.
Oh, I see you.
Can I please just...
Oh, my God.
These enemies are spawning all the time.
Good thing I can remove this, huh?
Unnecessary damage there.
I just avoided that damage.
Fuck you.
Okay.
Dude, this place is big.
Another water bolt.
Okay, we're fine.
I'm focusing so hard right now.
MLG gaming right here.
Ah, I didn't mean to click that button.
That's the thing I hate about this item, man.
Hey.
Oh, nice.
That was kind of cool.
Angry bones, huh?
Is this going to collapse?
No.
Okay, yeah, it is.
Whoa.
Barely held on there.
There we go.
Angry bones banner.
Oh, wait. I just realized.
Am I getting that after I kill a certain amount of them?
It's not a drop.
It's actually like a reward.
I need some kind of blood key for this.
I'm kind of demon key.
Can I open this?
Yes, sir.
Hold on.
Can you please give me a moment's rest?
My goodness.
You know what?
Real quick.
There is an option to auto pause.
You know what? I'm going to have this on.
I hate
having to rush through this
when I look at chests.
I want to take my time here.
I should be using something.
Uh...
No, remove that.
I need to do this.
Oh, wait. That's the limitation.
I can't.
How do I...
How do I actually...
Do I have to do this every time?
Okay.
All right. That's fine, I guess.
Let's see. What do I want to keep?
Just do this first.
And then
take the things we actually want.
I don't want any of this right now.
This one, I guess.
In case I see a shadow chest.
This one.
Metal shelf.
Can go away.
Okay. This looks good.
Should I remove any of these, I wonder?
Hmm.
This one can go in here.
Honestly, so can this.
And
This one is well right now.
And this.
Maybe I do want this.
I'm going to need to knock back and fire blocks.
Increases the lock of the user.
You know what? I'm going to try and use this.
And I'm going to use one of these.
Increase my lock.
Good stuff.
I do want the bookshelf.
Wait, these ones are glowing now.
Oh, never mind.
It's because I took the potion.
I thought they were like improved spikes.
Or something.
How am I going to get to that guy?
That's annoying.
There we go. He came to me.
Rookie mistake on his part there.
Move along. Actually, I want to try this.
Oh.
This is not bad at all.
In fact, this is pretty neat.
This does good damage.
But honestly, the gun is still.
It's still the best.
I don't know.
For close quarters like this, maybe this is actually better.
Yeah, look at that.
Oh.
That was satisfying.
Green dungeon bookcase.
Oh, is that a button?
Look, it's linked to that.
I see it now.
The mages are pissing me off.
Didn't mean to do that.
Move just now.
I chopped off the damn button.
I'm actually going to die here.
I'm not... I don't believe it.
Let me do this.
Oh, wait, I can't do it.
Let's do that.
B.
You're fucking...
We're going to heal up here.
We're going to chill for a bit.
And I will remove this.
Oh, you're not going to do that, are you?
Get rid of this shit.
Get rid of that.
And delete these.
I actually liked the game pause as well.
It's just a little bit annoying that I can't just instantly use any item in the...
But that's the thing.
Whoa!
Guarding telecounter.
This plays how many monsters have been killed.
Ah.
That can go on...
My other loadout.
Let's replace it with that, I guess.
And then on the third one we can put in...
Where did it just go?
There.
Put it there.
This is the mushroom set.
What's this?
Oil rack scones.
Cool.
Bone welder.
Oh, I have this.
And a blue moon.
But this is a way better one.
I can sell it though, so that's nice.
Put these in here.
Put this in there.
I'm going to keep my inventory super...
Ah, let's delete it.
I already have one.
Put this one in.
Okay.
You know what? I should...
Worst case, I should remove these chests.
Why can't I...
Ah, there we go.
I want to delete the chests
because that way I don't think
there's something in there.
Later on, if I come back here.
That was a bit risky.
Advanced strategies here.
What is that?
Did I say necromantic?
Necromantic sign.
What is this?
Marching bones.
Oh, this may actually be good to have here.
Yeah, let's just keep that there.
Oh god.
Let's heal up a bit.
Let's see.
I want to go up here a bit.
Oh, no.
Don't even think about it.
I saw you.
Oh, I didn't see you.
I'm taking way too much damage
trying to do this.
There we go.
God damn it.
Marching bones.
Ah, just put it back.
Where am I now?
I think we're looping around here a bit.
I didn't mean to do that.
Honestly, I hate this
fucking item right here.
I want to check real quick
if there's a setting to avoid the double-click bullshit
because I hate that so much.
There's got to be a way to make it a keybind instead.
Instead of...
That is just horrible.
Uh...
Is there something like that?
It's got to... wait.
Lock on priority?
This is just keybinds
so I don't think this is it.
Unfortunately.
Auto-select. Maybe there's a toggle
on something.
No.
Honestly, I'm going to have to
remove it.
I hate it so much
that I actually don't want it equipped.
It's messing with me more than it's helping me.
Put on something else.
This one could... actually this one, I guess.
What else do I have?
Nothing else. Okay.
Oh, wait. I still...
Hold on. What is giving me the ability to do this?
Am I crazy?
Wait a minute.
That's a chance to create illusions and dodge an attack.
Temporarily increase critical chance after dodge.
Oh, wait. No, no. It's not this one. Oh my god. I'm an idiot.
It's this one.
That's the one.
Oh my god.
Oh, so nice.
Beautiful. Finally.
Oh, that was such a pain in the ass.
Now I can play the game. Holy crap.
Oh, I feel so free now.
I don't have to worry about it.
That's lovely.
I need to heal.
Oh, I can't yet.
Okay.
Okay, so I'm looping back here now.
There was a little bit of a loop there.
That's okay. I'm going to go down again.
Yep. See.
Get off of me.
Are you going to come here?
Also, am I running out of potions?
No, I have 12 left. Okay.
Whoopsie.
Dark caster banner.
Yeah, look, because I defeated 50th.
It's definitely a reward for that. Oh god, here they come.
Let's actually do that.
Place it, please.
There we go.
Oh my god, they're everywhere.
Wow.
That was a good amount of damage just now.
Bro, what's with the casters?
I wonder if you, when you defeat a certain amount,
if the chance of them spawning increases.
Because this is very...
crazy.
How many there are.
Now we go down.
Oh my god, please fuck off.
That got fucking sent.
Amazing.
That's a danger. Look at this.
Come on.
Why is it not collapsing?
Look at that.
Thank you, potion.
Oh god, what am I doing?
Can I just actually do this?
Oh wow.
It keeps throwing it, even when I'm holding it.
That's actually pretty neat.
Hey, I'm warming up to the violent bone glove.
What is that?
Ragged brotherhood.
I wish I just... oh, actually.
I think there is a way.
Let's see here.
Let's search.
Let's say skeleton.
Skeletron.
Can I see its association?
Oh, wait a minute.
I get to see what they drop.
Treasure bag.
There's a 14% chance to get Chippy's couch.
Okay.
I want to see what they're associated with,
so I know which banner to use.
But I'm assuming marching bones.
Skeleton merchant?
He just wants to sell supplies,
such as rare torches and yo-yo gear.
Okay.
That sounds pretty nice.
Dude, the explosive bunny?
I...
I tried this. Why can't I...
Got them close. This is so confusing, by the way.
This doesn't close the window.
It closes what you're riding here.
So if I were to go and you click this.
But it's so universal to have a button up here
to close the window and not the button down here.
So it's like messing with my brain.
It's so weird.
I need to get used to that.
Okay. I kind of want to collapse all this.
What is hiding up here?
Oh, you know, I just realizing
the laser is not actually breaking this.
It's the little thing that...
This one, that's actually breaking it.
That just occurred to me.
See?
Oh, man. Look at all this stuff up here.
Guys, can you please just leave me alone for a goddamn second?
Holy crap.
Okay. Let me go up here.
I need to remove all this.
What is that? Is that a trap?
Dungeons? No, it's a shelf.
Okay. Deleted.
Look at that.
Diabolist lamp.
You got to represent the demons here.
We should have a demon room.
Reserved for demons.
Slowly making our way up here.
Man, I want to find the keys to
one of the chests up there.
Not this one, but okay.
Valor?
Yo-yo.
Maybe we should try the yo-yo stuff again.
Night owl.
Let's use one of them, I guess.
Recall.
Nope.
Delete this.
Bring out that.
Deposit all.
Quick stack, I guess.
Banners go in.
This one goes in.
Actually, keep it here in case I actually want to
put it on for whatever reason.
What is this actually?
Dash, double tap.
Yeah.
It sucks.
Danger sense.
Night owl. Let me use that.
There we go.
Dude, this place is
fucking massive.
The thing I don't understand
Oh, let me actually
When I came to this place first
the old man was like
you have to do something
fight me or whatever, right?
To gain entrance.
I will let you win.
But I could have just gone down.
Like the door was unlocked.
So maybe I didn't actually have to fight the guy.
I mean, I'm glad I did
because I got items from it.
And it was kind of cool, but you know.
Heal.
Um, spiky ball.
I wonder if I can destroy that with a bomb.
Oh god. Oh god!
No. Alright.
Where's the try?
What is that sound?
Is that you, sir?
Ah, they were so annoying.
I gotta keep moving.
Too bad the skeletons don't get hit by the
spiky ball here.
Okay, here's my shot.
Oh my god, they're so annoying!
Go!
Enter!
Kill him!
What's that?
Alchemy table!
Brother!
What is this?
Uh...
Oh, there you are.
Pot statue.
Hey!
See, nice!
My violin bone glove right now just
killed it.
What do we got in here?
Also, let me see.
Uh, can be placed.
33% chance to not consume potion
crafting ingredients.
That's awesome!
I like it!
That guy just got fucked.
Look at this awesome little pig.
Picture!
Skellington Jay Skellington.
Swirth.
W Garner.
What is this again?
Necromantic sign.
Whatever.
Put it.
Give me all of these. Uh, not that one.
Oh, here we go!
Oh, I need a green key for that!
Kind of jungle key or something.
Uh, let's see here.
Whoop!
Maybe I should play like this.
Nah, it's so small one I do.
Maybe it's just a bit like that.
Ah, a bit more.
That's better.
Oy!
Okay, we're safe.
Golden key, nice!
Gold coin, thorns potion.
Oh!
That's nice!
Nice!
You know what, why not?
That seems like a good potion to have against these archers.
Or these mages, I guess.
Let me, ah, too late.
I wanted to test how much damage it did to them.
I think these skulls right here are the ones that cursed me earlier.
Making me unable to use any items.
Dungeon slime.
Oh!
Let me see.
Damage me?
Okay, it doesn't actually work on spells, it seems.
Maybe it's just physical.
Nice.
A key! A key!
Man, maybe there is a way to remove that.
I need to test.
This is a bit scary.
I need to do this bit by bit.
There we go.
It's not gonna reach me here.
Go.
If I stand here, it's gonna be fine, right?
What is, what is damaging me?
Oh, it's this little piece of shit there.
So if I stand here, I'm okay.
No, it doesn't work.
That's sad.
Go here.
Oh no.
Oh my god!
I'm dying!
He's up there.
Thank you.
Up!
Oh no, I still get hit.
Go.
Fuck off!
This is...
This is crazy!
Thank god I just evaded the damage there.
Okay.
Let's go down again.
Ah, shit!
Oh my god, I'm gonna die.
Where are these enemies coming from, bro?
Oh, are you kidding me?
It's fucking raining enemies!
Well, there goes the no death stream.
That's so sad.
God damn it.
How much did I lose my...
Oh, I need to go back and grab my money.
I gotta go back.
I need to go back and grab that money.
Also, it's shit weather.
Look at this.
What's this?
Whoa!
Did I just get massively propelled by wind?
That was awesome.
Whoa!
Wait, we're not actually faster than usual.
It just looks faster.
It's an optical illusion.
We gotta get that money back.
Also,
delete some things.
That's good.
Can I actually...
I kinda just want to destroy all the things.
Bro, is it just me or is the game super loud?
What the fuck?
Let's tone that down a little bit here.
Oh my god.
Come on.
You? Let me zoom in a bit.
Do I do less damage right now than usual?
I feel like my damage is...
less than normal.
I still can't open this.
Or this.
Is he just gonna follow me forever, by the way?
If I just try to outrun him?
I think he is.
God, that's annoying.
He's just gonna shoot me from up there.
Dang!
You know what?
I need to play zoomed out, otherwise I'm actually at a disadvantage.
It sucks, but...
just everything is so small.
Maybe I need to get closer to the screen here.
Let me move in a bit closer like that.
See if that helps.
I need to remove that.
There we go.
Oh! Can we open this?
Oh my god.
Let's see.
Another one of these.
Suspicious Eye Dynamite.
I feel like it's dynamite rare.
Whenever I find it, it's only a singular one.
As if, oh, this is a valuable piece of loot.
Better use it wisely.
Wait, I never went this way.
Oh no.
Oh my god, I'm standing...
See, this is the thing. I can't see shit.
I need to zoom in.
Sick dodge just now.
This thing's gonna come back and fuck me.
I know it.
Get away!
Nice!
A nasty Muramasa.
Very fast speed.
Another shadow key.
I need to try these different weapons here, man.
I'm gonna have a weapon testing session later.
Another spelunker.
Fuck off with that.
What am I taking damage from?
Oh, they're dropping from the...
Goddamn ceiling again.
Wait, the...
Is the skull being thrown here?
Going through walls?
Seems like it is. Almost.
Got it.
Oh my god, I'm so low here.
Oh wait, did I leave my thingies somewhere?
I think I did.
Oh my god, you came out of nowhere.
Please, please, please!
Oh my god!
I'm actually gonna die here.
I'm gonna try this for now.
Let's chill for a second.
Wait, if there's a mage coming now, I'm dead.
I need to keep my options open.
30 seconds until heal?
Oh god!
Oh shit, I can't even...
This is gonna...
Yeah, perfect. Good.
Also, this is a trap right here.
Oh my god!
Heal up, heal up, heal up.
Come on, 5 seconds.
What is that right there?
A switch.
No!
Hold on, why am I so slow suddenly?
Water candle increased monster spawn rate?
What the fuck is that?
Where?
Where do we have a monster?
Water candle.
I need to dispatch of that water candle.
Where the fuck did I go last time?
I don't remember where I died.
Oh, up there.
Oh shit, okay, I'm on the wrong path here completely.
Okay, I'm not in range of it now.
There's something somewhere.
Also, there's a chest there.
Jolly jamboree!
My goodness!
The enemies are relentless.
Lock myself in.
Oh, this is probably not the best idea.
I'm realizing.
Kill him!
Oh god!
Jesus Christ!
I gotta get the fuck out of here!
Bro!
Is it getting worse?
What is this?
Oh, it's the thing.
Just run.
Fuck you.
Go!
Wait.
Wrong way! Wrong way!
Oh god.
Give me that.
Wait, is this it?
Oh my god.
There's so many enemies.
This game is difficult.
Where did I?
Up and left.
Left.
Okay.
Up, up, up, up, up, up.
Oh, he's so annoying.
Come on.
I'm so tense, dude.
Nice.
Is that it? Hold on, let me...
It is!
Holding this may attract unwanted attention.
Oh god.
Okay.
That's good to know, though.
Wait a minute.
Where did I die exactly? I died here.
Where's my money?
Where'd he go?
I'm losing my mind.
Where did it go?
Oh, let me remove this.
Okay. There's this one here, too.
There's more.
Somewhere. Up there.
God damn it.
I should have done this from the beginning.
I do wonder how much of an impact that does.
Removing these.
There. Gone. I still have the effect.
There's something else somewhere.
There.
There we go.
We've got still more, though.
This, I remember.
Okay, nice.
Nice. Okay, the effect is gone.
Okay, so look. No enemies.
That's fantastic.
That's so important, though.
Where is my money?
I have no idea, dude.
Did I not die there?
Did I die? I kind of forgot now.
What's this?
We don't have a candle.
I don't know what's causing this. What's that?
What?
Quick, quick, quick.
Just keep going.
Remove these hazards.
There.
Get rid of that.
Whoa!
Hold on, I think we need this.
Oh, man.
Hot damn.
That was scary.
We have a candle.
Oh, shit!
Oh!
Run!
Ha!
Holy crap.
Okay, that room...
was horrible.
Get out of here.
Hold on, I need to...
You know?
I need to apply all kinds of buffs.
Let's do it after this.
I'm not strong enough.
Get rid of all this bullshit.
There it is.
Oh, we'll destroy this.
See ya, bitches!
Nice.
What's that?
Oh, you can see nearby hazards.
Okay.
Dude, this dungeon is fucking awesome.
I'm having so much fun with this.
A cream soda!
It's so fizzy. Cheers, everybody!
Oh, yeah. I'm going to drink that.
There we go.
And delete that.
The dynamite.
Yeah.
Let's be careful here.
Oh, this is actually...
Annoying. I can't remove this until the chest is gone.
Why can't I click on it?
Oh, now I can. Weird.
Bro, sometimes my inventory doesn't work.
Like, I have to reload.
That's so weird.
I don't know if you know what I mean at all, but...
That right there needs to go.
I thought that would collapse for sure.
Also, I've been here before.
No, I haven't.
A cursed skull banner.
Cool.
God damn it.
Get rid of the danger.
Thank you.
Okay, um...
Looks like we have cleaned out this place.
There's still more up there.
Did I ever get my...
I never got my money. I don't understand.
What the fuck did the money go?
Also, I need to...
Quickly deposit some stuff.
Quick stack, and I need to take some potions.
I brought some, didn't I?
Uh, sure. Let's do that one.
Only one of them.
Actually, I thought I had more potions on me.
Slow's falling speed?
That could be...
Let's try it.
Oh, and there's a candle somewhere.
Where?
Also, is that a pot for me?
Green dungeon vase.
Oh, yeah, I'm falling slow. Holy shit.
Wow.
That's very unpredictable.
I can't get used to that.
But I guess it'll keep me safe.
But it can also mess with me.
Is the game paused while I'm...
I don't think it's paused while I'm on the map.
I need to go down there and check out what's going on there.
For sure.
That room looked insane.
Falling like this, though.
Very nice.
Oh, a key. Thank you.
Now, let's see here.
Can I?
I definitely can. Check this out.
Oh, no.
I'm in a very precarious position here.
There we go.
Clean up all this.
I don't want it.
This whole place is evil.
And it needs to be perched.
Okay, now I feel better.
Okay.
That made me happy.
Now...
Wait, does it actually... hold on.
The map is so confusing to me.
I need to get to the bottom of what those lines mean.
So, obviously, there's something going on down here.
I can't really...
get through this.
And the slow falling actually helps when you rise as well.
Like when you use this.
Let me keep going up here.
Hold on.
Let me actually remove this.
Delete that.
What?
Uh...
I don't know about that, guys.
Seems a little...
Suspect to me.
What the fuck?
Sigmund!
Humble grumble.
Nice.
He's such a cutie.
With a party hat on.
How you doing?
Look, look.
Okay.
You're gonna make your way back to the...
to the town.
The Hankman.
This is...
This is the hard part.
Don't stand there.
Ah, stop!
Stop making it difficult for me.
Ah, wait a minute. This is horrible.
Oh, wait. Is there a candle nearby?
There is.
Uh, it's gotta be down here somewhere.
Let's find the candle.
Ah!
Ah, I need to get the fuck out of here.
Holy shit!
Okay, I'm not next to a candle anymore.
Let's chill here for a bit.
Oh, man.
Let's see.
I have 17 seconds on the potion.
Come on, come on.
Give me.
I'm gonna have a campfire in here or something.
Doesn't look like it.
Where?
Ah, there you are.
Ah, I hate the...
God damn casters.
Okay, I healed.
I need to heal up to Max here.
I'm so tense.
Holy shit!
Some reason my shoulders are locked.
They're like, completely
tense when I play this game.
It's constant, uh...
Close calls here.
I'm close to the candle now again.
I have to make a run for it.
Ah, this is...
terrible.
Where's the candle?
Let's loot it.
A masterful magic missile.
Casts a controllable missile.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Just take it all.
Titan potion, sure.
All of it.
Come on.
No, what?
How did I just die?
Are you kidding me?
Okay, my gold is right here now.
It's right there on that shelf.
I was going for this stupid candle up there.
Let me quickly go back to the town.
Come on.
I need to deposit.
And...
delete that.
Ah, wait.
Let me turn this off on again.
All to pause off.
There, painting for you.
Skellington Jay Skelling's worth.
Goes there.
Alchemy table.
Let's put that in here.
Let me remove these two.
There.
This is the alchemy room.
Yeah, just delete these, I guess.
Green dungeon lamp.
I mean...
Nah.
Four golden keys.
Let's put some banners.
We don't need two of them.
There.
We got a represent.
Dungeon boss.
I feel like that would fit well in here.
But why can't I put this in front of the painting?
I think you want this here, don't you?
By the way, Seymour.
Storm's rolling in. How about you come in and buy something?
I was planning on it.
What do you actually sell?
Are you selling anything new?
A safe.
Safe.
Huh.
I kind of want to buy it, but this...
I'm so low on gold.
By the way, how much gold do I have in my...
Oh, I hit... oh, shit.
Oh, I should put my gold in here, man.
Fuck me.
That's what I should have done.
Oh, wait a minute. Didn't I put my gold inside one of these chests?
At some point?
Am I dreaming things?
I feel like I put some gold in here at some point.
I don't think it's there anymore.
Crap.
Welp.
Titan potion.
Masterful magic missile.
Let me try that and let me also try this.
I got some new weapons here.
Whoa!
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, look!
Yo, that's pretty cool!
Wait, how does that work?
Can I move it? It's like a yo-yo?
Hold on a second now.
Oh, yeah!
Then we have this sword.
I mean, a nasty Muramasa.
I mean, it attacks pretty quick, I guess.
It's not bad.
It's kind of good.
Then we have this one.
Valor.
I got to try all these weapons, man.
Masterful magic missile.
This seems pretty cool.
Also, it's a material. Hold on a second.
Sky fracture.
Yeah, I don't have any of these souls.
Okay, good to know, though.
Good to know.
What about...
This one?
Alright, I can do this again if I want to, but I don't want to.
This was not a thingy, right?
No.
Is this a material or something?
Poisoned? Yeah, okay.
Let me put this lamp somewhere.
There.
This is a very crowded looking place, I realize.
It is what it is, man.
Buy that, please.
And this...
Buy that, too.
Don't come...
complaining if you suddenly enemies are spawning, okay?
You bought it.
Just saying.
Now.
Bones.
In.
Ooh, I have a lot of bones.
Now I'm starting to think.
Did I have bones?
Already?
Before I found them down there.
I may have had it, I don't know.
Let's put some stuff down.
In here, I want to put this now.
And I want to keep these.
The Titan potion.
Increases knockback.
Do I really want that, though?
This one is sick.
Like, this weapon right here is actually
insane.
I don't understand why it says very slow.
It's not that slow, it's like, really quick.
But here's the thing, maybe the animation
is not directly tied to the attack speed.
Like, I felt like I did a lot of damage
with the nasty Muramasa.
Even though it only has 25
damage per swing.
It does save very fast speed, right?
In fact, I can test that right now.
Approximately...
Okay.
I need that TPS item.
It's definitely faster.
It may be comparable, actually.
It could be.
It could be comparable.
Then we have this.
This.
Which, on average, is insane for a
ranged weapon. Just look at this.
Unreal. This one.
Not bad, either. This is
pretty sick.
I like it.
Oh, this one.
Oh, this is
using mana.
Like, there's no tomorrow.
Maybe that's a nice thing to use
and then switch over to another weapon.
Empty mana. Switch weapon.
So you would go like this
and then when it's ready
you go like that. Maximum damage.
Switch back. Recharge.
That could be a strategy.
Let me put the shield in here.
I don't need that right now.
I should also be using this
more. I don't really use it.
Oh, and healing potions!
I'm about to run out.
Holy shit.
I need
this for that. And then I also need
this.
And this.
And I think that may be it.
But now that we have this
it's gonna increase chance of not using materials.
Nice.
Now, what was the recipe
for just crafting a healing potion?
Can you tell me?
Mushroom and gel.
Gotcha. Oh, I've got that.
Not a lot of mushroom though.
I wonder if this will work.
Probably not, right?
No.
Nice.
Make a bunch of that and then...
Wait, if you look at the
icon for this one
it got stuck sometimes because
it didn't get used in the process
and that's this table doing that.
That's freaking fantastic.
Potions.
Nope.
Organics. In.
In.
Potions. There.
Okay!
Now, what else did I have for weapons here?
Forceful Aqua Scepter.
Demonic Harpoon.
Explosive Trap Rot.
This is 17.
This is 28.
That's definitely faster.
Man, what does that little icon mean
underneath the weak knockback?
I wonder what that means.
Will this have the same?
No, okay, so there is something going on there.
Dangerous Mandible Blade.
We've got Goldfish
hanging out.
Where did I put my
Loot All?
Quick Stack.
All Skeletons.
Let's put that
here. It's Halloween.
Have fun, guys.
Then we have Gothic Bookcases.
There we go.
Let's decorate this shit a little bit.
Wait, I can't.
Oh, it's blocking.
Okay, I see.
That's not a good idea then.
And you go.
Jester Zero.
Put that
there, I guess.
These ones can go in here.
Oh, Bone Banners.
Oh, this one goes in here as well.
Then we have this one.
Goddamn inventory, man.
I have ballast lamp.
Let's hang that somewhere.
There.
This is starting to look like a hoarder's room.
Now, did I have more inside my...
Oh, these don't stack.
That's interesting.
Oh, this is full now.
Oh, no.
We'll have to resort to this.
Nah. This goes out.
This goes in.
I
want to sell some shit here.
The dupe lamp and all these can be sold.
I don't need this.
Get rid of these shitty weapons.
I'm selling all this.
Actually, anything that's not a material, I guess.
And that I don't want.
This one, though, is kind of interesting.
I'm gonna keep that.
Alright, let's sell this.
Please take this one.
This one.
That one.
Ah, yeah.
Cleaning up and gaining money. That's good.
Good.
Also this one.
You know what? You can have that as well.
And that.
I think I'm good for now.
Now, we have to open this.
Put in these.
Put in the potions.
And these two.
That one.
Actually, this one can stay here.
No. Maybe I want to experiment with it.
Yeah, keep it.
Alright.
Let's go back.
Off we go.
Man, holy shit, look how big this is!
Maybe I should plan my route while I look here.
Let's see here.
So, I died there.
And this is
a really fucked up place.
This is so hard to get through.
No, this was the place.
But there's something up here.
But isn't there more downstairs?
Excuse me.
Wow.
How rude.
Oh, I'm standing still!
Oh!
I was like, why am I not moving?
There's actually a bit more here as well.
That connects.
Probably not a lot.
This one seems done and dusted in this area.
Definitely something here.
And I need to find keys for the remaining chests.
There's an icy chest
and a green chest
and also a special chest
in the very beginning.
Yeah.
Dude, I wonder if I can craft the potion
that teleports me randomly.
That would be so much fun. I want to craft those.
And I want to take this with me.
And that.
Thank you.
Oh.
These go here.
There we go.
I'm going to experiment with this wand.
Wait, we have a worm?
Why are we so slow suddenly?
Probably because we need some...
a flat surface.
Oh, you like magic?
Come here. Let me show you something.
What do you think of that?
Oh, wait.
Actually, not bad at all.
Yo, wait.
Is there an AoE on that?
It looked to me like there was an AoE.
Oh, get rid of these.
God damn thingies.
Holy crap.
Oh, yeah.
Get rid of all these.
Oh, my.
Bro, this magic missile here is fun.
Let me actually play with the yo-yo a bit here.
Another candle.
Let me get rid of this.
Let's also activate this again.
Wait, are they homing? They're homing!
Holy shit!
This is amazing!
Oh, yeah, bro!
Yo, that's freaking great.
I feel like I may have found my new favorite weapon.
Is that crazy?
Oh, my God!
Do we have a candle here or something?
Down here. There's a candle down here.
Also, I never went down here, actually.
Oh, my God. This is so good.
Remove this.
Oh!
Oh, I didn't mean to do that, but okay.
That works.
Oh!
Bro, you can go like this
and then go upside here and run like this.
Oh!
Ho, ho, ho, ho!
That's cool!
Uh, come here.
Am I out of mana? Why can't I shoot?
Oh, wait!
Wait, did it use ammo?
Oh, no, wait a minute.
It uses 12 mana.
Oh!
I thought it was a forever thing.
Oh, no.
I was so happy with this.
Oh, well.
Back to the sapper.
And I guess the yo-yo as well.
Bro, you can just...
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, fine.
The sapper is my...
my friend still.
I'm good friends with the sapper.
I'm gonna go down here.
A whole new area. Look at this.
Oh, you know what? No, no, no, no, no, no.
I need to collect my money.
Let's not be dumb about this.
Let's play it smart.
And find the damn candle.
Is it in here?
Wait. No, it's not.
Must be up here.
No, I don't see it.
Okay, I'm out of range of the candle now.
Still out of range.
What's up with the flaming wheels?
There's so many.
Bro, what is happening?
Oh, god.
There's too many enemies.
We are leaving.
Fuck this.
I'm getting completely overwhelmed here.
Get the fuck out of here.
Oh, yeah, look at this.
This is home.
Ah! Remove that candle.
Dude, I just removed the candle.
Why are there so many of you?
What is going on?
Bring me from this torment.
I just need to heal.
Actually, wait a minute. Did I go down there?
Oh, I did not.
But wait, I have to collect my money.
Don't be dumb about...
Actually, there's a chest. Hold on.
What do we got?
A handgun.
It's a material.
Cream soda.
Drinking that for sure.
Look, look, look.
Okay, don't go down there yet.
Gotta collect.
Where was it? Up here.
Also, wait a minute. There's stuff going on here.
This is amazing for doing this.
A little scary though.
Why can't I...
There we go.
Huh.
Look at this.
Shortcut unlocked?
Get rid of that candle immediately.
Any more candles?
Oh, this is where I died.
There's my money. I got it.
Fuck yeah, we're safe.
Oh my, there's so many enemies.
This is where I lied last time as well.
Let's not die again.
Nice, that's kind of cozy.
Regen.
In fact, I have an idea here.
I should be doing this all the time.
Like...
Please.
Like, because I can shoot up and down through it.
It's...
It's a solid strategy.
Just...
Go like this, because this is amazing.
Ah, there you are.
Okay.
Things are starting to look up here.
We're in a good spot.
No, no, no, no, no.
I did loot that chest. Let's remove it.
There's a chest there.
What do we got?
Another handgun.
Dynamite, Justice Arrow, Spelunker...
Thorns.
You know what? I'm going to put the thorns on.
And then I'm also going to...
Wait, I have another one of these?
Clothier Voodoo Doll.
Let's also drink that.
Oh! What is that?
There's something in there.
Is that gold?
Oh, look at all the enemies.
We're not even near a candle.
This is crazy.
See, here's where I want to make a...
Actually, let me put that there.
Just like that.
Now I can shoot everywhere.
Dude, the platforms are...
A great item.
Ah!
Let me snipe you.
There we go. Give me that HP.
Is there a candle here somewhere?
Why is everyone so angry?
Just go up and to the right.
Oh, look it up there!
Whoa!
Oh!
Another one of those trap places.
Do we have a...
Slowfall thingy?
Doesn't look like it.
Ah, shit.
Is this gonna be a little...
sketchy?
Make some light.
Why can't I place this?
Ah, there we go.
Just take a quick look down there.
Oh, nice! I can still do it without Slowfall.
Oh!
Oh, it's just a...
It's just a fucking death pit.
There's nothing down there.
Another one of these.
Oh, wait, is things collapsing here?
What, the door?
It is a door.
Interesting.
Whoa!
Hey!
Oh, where are you?
Show yourself.
There you are.
How do I get in there up there?
What is that?
Right there. Is that gold?
Let's try going this way.
This is actually pretty cool.
That's a cool mechanic the way you can do this.
Do we have another candle?
Yep!
Where'd you come from?
Look at that!
Painting is glowing.
Oh, wait, is that because of my potion?
Probably is.
I just realized a better way to get through this.
Just use the damn platforms.
Give me that.
Wait, are they glowing like that?
Because they're actually worth a lot of money or something?
Maybe I can sell it to a merchant for a lot of money.
Green dungeon bathtub?
How about no?
Ah, damn it.
I got hit by that.
Wait, where did you come from?
We need to do an emergency...
situation here.
There. We're hanging out.
We're chilling. Oh, wait, there's actually a blue candle.
Somewhere here.
Probably up here somewhere.
No, not that I can see.
What's what we got here? An unpleasant Morimasa.
You know what? Invisibility potion?
That doesn't sound too shabby now, does it?
Where did it go?
There.
Drink that.
Be stealthy.
What just hit me?
God damn it.
What?
I can't shoot.
Why can't I shoot?
Now I can shoot again.
What the fuck? That was weird.
Is that a bug?
What am I... Oh, it's the trap!
You goddamn piece of shit.
Unreal.
Let's regen a bit.
But where is this candle at?
Must be down here somewhere.
There it is. Let's go take care of it immediately.
Otherwise they're gonna keep coming.
And we're not gonna have a great time!
Holy shit.
Get back up here.
Okay. There's still a candle.
And there's a trap messing with me.
Where the heck is it?
Did I miss one down here?
Probably not.
God damn it, I have no clue.
I'm gonna keep going down.
Oh wait, a seed is there!
Oh my god.
I need to heal bad.
Get rid of it!
Okay, it's gone. It's gone.
Oh man.
What the hell is that? A bone wand.
Consumes bone.
Is that a turret?
I don't understand.
I am clueless as to what that is.
Okay, I need to heal up here now.
Now that we finally got rid
of that candle.
Just chillax for a second here.
That's enough chilling.
Let's go.
Nice. Oh, this is all gonna collapse.
Isn't it?
Sure is.
So is this a big death pit or what?
Let me throw some lights down there.
There we go.
Also, deposit all honestly.
What do I want to keep? I guess these are good to have.
And this one maybe.
Dynamite.
I'll keep that here. I don't know what I'm using.
What I'm doing with a diamond. I mean, it's a material.
I'm gonna collect it, I guess.
Build something with it.
Get rid of all the useless items here.
Green dungeon candle.
I do want to keep those actually.
Imagine how confusing it is to use a gravitation potion inside of here.
That doesn't sound very good.
Where's the campfire there?
Let's do this now.
And this one.
Oh, wait. Oh, that's interesting.
When you have this on, you're not actually breaking this.
That's cool.
All right.
Sort of.
Let's go.
What do we got? Oh, yeah, it's death.
That is death.
Giant death pit.
What is that up there?
Man, I wonder...
So...
What is happening here?
Interesting.
How is that wired, though?
What the term is the...
Seekity sack?
Okay.
Nothing else down there, it seems.
I'm going to see some wall here I can break.
Maybe not.
Did I just realize something? Hold on.
Oh, I just realized that if you jump and you hold down immediately after, you won't jump as high.
Look.
But if I just jump, it goes into the ceiling.
That's a way to avoid these spikes when you have slow fold.
Where to go? Where to go? Where to go?
There was a path down here that I wanted to try.
Let's try that.
Also, before I forget,
let me fill up my...
with money.
There we go. Just in case I die.
I have a plate safe.
Is there a candle here?
There's not.
For some reason, there's just a lot of enemies.
Fuck off with this!
I want to find more breakable wall.
This was the death pit.
So there's a switch here.
Oh, it's a weird how they're...
They've been wiring this in here.
What is that?
Rustic company standard.
I think there's a bunch of different factions, huh?
So now I want to go down pretty much.
Go!
I'm so slow!
I'm okay.
I like shooting while falling.
Seems cool.
Ah, be careful.
Heal.
I can break some things here.
Okay, now I'm back to where I was. That's good.
Here, and then we go down.
Looks like if you open the...
the loading screen there too quickly,
the menu is unresponsive.
I don't know if that's a bug or intended.
Seems a little weird.
Pretty consistent.
Look at that nice painting.
Another one of these. Let me take it.
Water bolt? Does that count as...
No.
Ah!
Okay, now we're back here.
Go!
No fear.
No fear. This is death, isn't it?
Yep, it is.
Gimme that, though! That's a duck!
Powered by birds!
Ooh, that looks scary.
Okay, that's a safe spot. Good.
Did I have bombs?
Not right now.
Let me use this.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Another key, thank you.
Ooh, what's that?
Bewitching table.
Right click to have more minions.
Oh, so wait, if I summon Abigail and I click on this, I make more?
Is that what I'm supposed to be...
getting from that?
I'm taking both.
Thank you.
That's a trap!
Get rid of that shit.
Nobody wants that!
Okay.
Let's think. What do I suffer from?
Poisoned. And a candle somewhere.
So are these fucking enemies hydro-powered or what?
They're hydro-homies.
The water sustains them.
That's a trap!
I'm not even gonna take these things.
Even though I want to.
Jesus, you were a master of avoiding.
This looks cool. I will take that.
Give me that HP.
There we go.
Shit!
Dude, this weapon has been my bread and butter.
But I think it would do pretty well with this one as well.
Let me just use that for a bit actually.
Let's see how it goes.
Dude, this dungeon
just goes on forever.
It's freaking awesome!
Can I get some keys please for the chests upstairs?
Is that a possibility at all?
Stop killing me!
Everything in here wants to kill me.
There's the button.
Look at that.
Fucking hell.
There you are.
What do we got?
Another magic missile.
Let's see here.
Will it say how many
shots I have left?
Wait, did I use something in my inventory for that?
Wait a second.
Oh no, never mind.
I thought it was using jester's arrow.
But it's not.
Okay.
At least these shelves.
Shadow key, jester's arrow.
Night owl.
This one though?
I'll try. Let me just
see that again.
Okay, that's actually pretty neat.
It's pretty nice.
I think I've had this before.
Found this somewhere.
Hey!
I need to make an emergency
healing station here.
There we go.
I hate those things!
I hate that thing.
What's happening over there?
Hold on.
Oh, that's lava.
Here they come.
Is there a candle nearby or something?
There we go.
Hey.
You.
Stop that.
You know, using this weapon right here
is actually pretty nice because
it blocks all the projectiles coming towards me.
Like, look at this. This is really nice.
This does a ton of damage.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This weapon is totally amazing.
I'm blocking all these.
This is arguably safer than the ranged weapon.
This is so good, holy shit!
I've been sleeping on this.
Does this really not lead to anything?
I almost can't believe that.
Oh, what the fuck? Now it works?
What the heck?
Look at you.
Angry bones.
Oh wait, now I'm here again.
Oh!
Dude, this place is crazy.
Oh, there's also something over there.
Ah, but wait, you know what?
I just remembered, holy shit.
It's already been three and a something hours.
I'm gonna take a break now
and eat some food.
And also quickly before I go here
has the audio been okay?
Has there been any issues with the stream at all?
Is everything smooth sailing?
Or is it...
Is everything good?
I'm gonna open chat and then I'm gonna take a break
and I'll be back after eating.
Probably like 15 minutes I would have imagined.
20 minutes tops.
I'm gonna keep playing.
Okay, I'm opening chat.
Audio is great. Everything works.
Everything good?
It's been all potatoes.
Is that now the cinnamon for good?
Potato?
Smooth sailing for audio?
I don't know about anything else though.
Okay, well, in that case...
Beautiful.
Good stuff.
I was about to say good stuff, Oliver.
But there is actually a guy in chat called Oliver.
Enjoy your break.
Yeah, I'll be back in like 15, 20 minutes.
I'm gonna put a timer.
I'll see you guys soon.
Yes, let me do the transition here.
There we go.
It's like 17 minutes.
I'll see you guys soon.
Had to grab another one, of course.
In fact, I was a little thirsty five minutes ago,
but I thought now I'm gonna save the cracking open the can.
How y'all doing, huh?
Oh man, dude, I feel so good today.
You know, you have one of those days where
you're just happy about everything.
I don't know, man. I just feel great.
How are you guys doing? Are you guys feeling good?
We have returned.
Indeed. Blair Daniels.
Haunter.
Aorta. What does aorta mean?
I feel like I've seen that word before.
I'm back. Welcome back, Mikey the Great.
Nico Comsy.
Oliver Horn. What's up, Oliver?
How you doing?
Aorta is in the heart. Oh!
Of course!
It's sort of close to artery.
Right? I guess there's a connection there with the words.
Aorta is the largest vein going into the heart.
Ah, okay, okay.
Gotcha.
Okay.
So I noticed something while
waiting.
I have an item here.
Precious?
No, precise?
Nassar.
Gives me immunity to curse.
So as far as I understand it,
curse is so you can't use any items.
And the skulls that fly around,
I think when they hit you,
they curse you.
So this will prevent that,
which is kind of cool.
Maybe it'll come in useful later.
It's also a material,
so I can craft something with it.
So I'm looking forward to trying
to see what I can do there.
That's actually one of the
best things about this game is
finding a new material
just to see what you can do with it, you know?
It's awesome.
Hmm.
I guess I can remove these.
What else can I remove?
I kind of want to keep these
weird items here.
I need them to, you know,
make the homes look nice
and homely.
Even though a dungeon vase
may not be the thing.
Actually, I don't know if it's
dungeon vase or dungeon vase.
I'm not sure.
What is this again?
You know, maybe I should also
look at these.
This is sort of the same as
Minecraft where the achievements
sort of guide you a little bit
on what to do.
There's all kinds of things here.
Yeah.
Discover a large bee's hive
deep in the jungle.
All kinds of things.
Craft a molten pickaxe.
This is nice, actually.
I'm going to refer back to this
when I'm truly stuck.
Okay.
Whoa!
Okay, we're back into it.
Let's see here.
I wish the game would pause
while I'm mapping here.
Alright, fine.
I guess it's not going to do that.
Hey!
What's up, guys?
This weapon is fantastic.
It's just incredible.
What's happening here?
What was I even doing?
Right, I just connected
this part up here.
And there's lava in there,
which is kind of interesting to me.
What is with the lava?
It's actually connecting to
another cave that is there.
Let's see if I can sort of
find a way in there.
Maybe there's some loose
stone.
Maybe here?
No.
You guys.
Actually, I'm going to test
if they hit me.
So I got hit.
I'm cursed.
Yeah.
Oh, I may actually die.
This may have been a bad idea.
I'm fine.
Yeah, don't get hit by these guys.
That's a bad idea.
Dude, the hook,
I need to be using that some more.
You can totally just reset the items here.
Which is nice.
What's happening here?
Let's see.
Where am I?
There!
That's where I need to go.
Oh my God!
Wait, did this thing just appear?
This wasn't here before!
What the fuck?
Either I'm losing my mind.
This thing wasn't here before.
Like, I'm talking 30 seconds ago.
What the actual fuck?
Can you leave me as...
Please, just one second.
Guys.
Uh...
Down, up, okay.
I guess I'm going this way.
There's so many enemies here.
I see you up there.
Go down here again.
Please set the enemies.
Okay.
This is where I came from before.
Oh yeah, I have to remember this too.
Gotta bring that.
Let's go.
And then when we go left now, we have to go down.
Hey, what's for you?
Uh, here.
Here we go.
This is new.
Oh, look at all that.
I should make the platform.
I don't have many more, I don't think.
Do I have...
Any wood?
I don't know, don't think so.
Oh, I need to take care of that immediately.
Let's see.
Valor.
Is that the same thing I already have?
Archery potion?
I'll leave that one.
Okay.
Oh, these are traps.
Right of those as well.
I wonder if there's a way to set a filter, sort of,
so that certain things you pick up
will always just get deleted.
Or maybe a way to just not pick up
a certain item ever again.
That would be pretty dope.
If there's a way to do that.
There's water here.
That's a death pit, isn't it?
It sure is.
So that's a dead end.
You know what?
There's actually enemies there.
How do I get in there?
Oh, I never destroyed this!
What the heck?
Oh, I got hit! I'm cursed!
I get it, I get it.
Oh, my God.
Get rid of these guys.
There we go.
Can I not get in there?
Oh, wait, I see it!
Oh, wait, it's the death pit in there.
Uh-huh.
That explains it.
Leave me alone for a second, guys.
Ah, crap.
That worked against me, though.
Oh, yeah.
I wanted to use this some more because it's actually sick.
Am I done exploring?
I feel like I should...
I'm expecting some kind of boss at the end of this.
That's what makes me think I'm not done with this place yet.
Then again, that was a boss at the beginning of it.
Maybe they reverted it here.
Like, no, fuck you, we're doing the boss first.
I don't see any other path, honestly.
So I think, for now, we're gonna head back.
Uh, here.
See ya!
I've got so many items, though.
And I've got money.
Do we have a trader here?
Let me actually see the...
Sigmund has left.
Wait a minute!
I found someone down there.
That I rescued.
Who then died?
I need to make, uh, more rooms.
I just remembered that.
Uh, let's actually do that first.
I mean, first we stack items here.
Like that.
And then, uh, quickly do this.
Also turn off this now.
Uh, loot all.
Deposit all.
Loot all.
And quick stack.
There we go.
Okay!
I'm gonna sell some of these.
Do I already have a handgun?
Sell that one as well.
Clintlock.
That sort of sucks.
Okay, time for inventory management.
Once more.
Oh wait, these are materials.
Let me keep one.
Bone wand.
Mmm.
Don't quite understand that one yet.
This one can go.
Can I quickly sort my items?
So, okay.
Eight silver for this.
Eight silver, eight.
Okay, so this is not that valuable.
You can have one of these.
Take these as well.
Powered by birds.
Okay.
I need to take some chests here.
There.
And...
Let's just do this for now.
Kind of want a light in here.
I'm not sure where to put that light.
This whole top row.
Maybe that can be something separate.
That's what I'm thinking.
Maybe all of this can be construction items.
You know?
Because construction is like all this random crap
I'm going to find so much of.
Let's do that.
Alchemy table.
The witching table.
I want to have one of these on me because I want to place it.
Cursed skull.
I have to organize this.
Detonator.
Weapons.
This one.
Wait, hold on.
This one has 9 ammo now.
No, never mind.
I'm an idiot.
It's because it's on the 9th key bind.
Did I run out of ammo or not?
I'm confused now.
Hold on a second.
Why did it not work earlier?
Alright.
The bone one.
Let me quickly test that again.
Oh, I guess I need bones.
So that is the ammo for this one.
It's straight up bones.
Now I have 19.
Alright.
Gotcha.
But what is the point of making bone pillars?
That's so weird.
But whatever.
Put it in accessories.
The precise Nassar.
Let's check that with Dylan.
Hey, Dylan.
What do you think about my Nassar?
A megaphone.
Makes counter-curse mantra.
Oh.
Pretty cool.
So I need to find a megaphone.
Neat.
For now, it goes in here.
Get in there, get in there.
Rolly, the traveling merchant has arrived.
Just in time.
I've got money to spend.
Where you at?
Let's see what you got.
Combination hookah and coffee maker.
Also makes julienne fries.
I don't know what julienne fries are actually.
Green team platform.
Lifeform analyzer.
Celestial wand.
Summons SD.
Wait, one platinum?
What is that? Is that 100 gold or something?
Is that a new currency?
Bro, what is a platinum?
Star princess crown is a vanity item.
This is 50 gold.
So this could easily be 100 gold, actually.
Do not eat the vile mushroom.
That's so true.
Let's get that.
Fancy dishes, any material?
I mean this one, but I already have it.
Drisken?
Maybe I should try this again, actually.
I feel like I've gotten more powerful, right?
So maybe the time to do it.
Oh, this is a big one.
Don't eat the bad mushroom.
Oh, you know what? We're going to put that in the new room I'm going to make.
Yeah, that's going to be in there.
Speaking of...
I should probably grab some wood.
So what I need is wood, wall,
and that's pretty much it.
In fact, I had an idea some time ago.
So I'm going to test that here.
Technically...
Oh, I need platforms.
Oh...
Do I have any just...
sitting here?
No. Okay, I'll make them fine.
Let's just make a bunch anyway.
Good. And also...
Whoops.
Excellent, the old set there.
There we go.
Like, if I just do that...
I can just jump.
But the problem is...
the NPCs cannot.
I'm afraid.
But I can.
The question is, will they be able to get up there?
Or not.
I'm going to test that now.
Because these damn stairs are actually annoying me so much.
You don't even know.
Like that.
I'm just going to make some extra room here.
May as well do it.
No.
Nah, that looks bad.
We can have a big room here.
Or you know what? It can just end here.
Make it a bit asymmetric.
Would look pretty neat as well.
Now, I'm afraid we need more wall.
Ah, we need a thingy for that.
It's annoying.
Wall.
Nice. That's a lot.
Oh yeah, this is so nice.
The smart cursor.
So comfortable.
I understand why they added this.
Or why this is a functionality to begin with.
I would have gone crazy having to put this all manually.
So...
Doors.
Let's wait with that.
Let's make the...
See here.
That's a door.
Let's do...
There.
Let's do a big separator here.
A little bit...
Not great looking because it's not really connected.
But we could connect it here and then...
Oh, you know what? That's actually not a bad idea.
I'm gonna do that.
I'm gonna do something like this, hold on.
Like that.
I don't want it to go all the way to the left, just...
Let's also remove this because it looks like shit!
There. And then we go like this now.
And we platform it.
Nice.
I can go like that.
Beautiful. I could even do that here.
Ooh.
Is that crazy?
Maybe just...
Maybe just that.
Jump up like this. Oh!
Nice.
Because then we can go down like this straight and build things.
Doors. Wait, don't we have specialized doors?
We have wooden doors. We have granite doors.
We have all the doors. Holy shit.
We have a skyware door.
I want to keep that.
Take this, take this, take this.
Take this, those, those, those.
We're gonna do all kinds of shit now.
It's gonna look amazing.
Chests and all kinds of crap.
Granite door.
That's fine.
Wall.
We also have some windows.
Stop it!
Make it a...
I don't know how to remove that.
There we go.
There we go. Okay. Everything's fine.
Okay.
Now.
There.
Actually, I don't like how that looks. Let's make this one big room.
These are big rooms.
These are four important guests.
Let's make a little thingy here.
Log it out.
No.
Make it...
Can I change the shape of it?
That's annoying.
Okay, you know what?
This is gonna seem petty, but...
It's an issue I have.
I'm gonna make it one taller.
Ah!
What did I just kill?
I'm so sorry.
Whoever that was.
Hopefully nobody's pet.
I just killed something again.
Oh, it's because it's throwing these things around!
Every time I use the thing.
Can I still jump up here?
Yeah, I can. Perfect.
This is one tall ass house.
Oh, nice.
Just filled out that as well. What is going on here?
Now, that's bad.
We need to put a thingy there.
I don't have stone!
That's okay.
I kind of want to replace these with wood anyway.
It doesn't look good.
Stop hitting random blocks!
I just realized...
I could just make platforms everywhere.
To make it super convenient everywhere.
Oh my god.
Is that crazy?
Is that too much?
Maybe it is.
Oh no.
Can I really...
There we go. Much better.
Much important.
And then...
There.
No, this is going to be a big room.
Yeah.
Now doors!
Plop! Plop!
Everywhere.
I'm also going to have one here.
Doors? Do-do-do-do-do-doors.
There.
Okay. Now we need a...
Sure, just use that.
That's fine.
Have a table here.
Have a table there.
And let's have a...
Oh, wait.
Huh?
Look at how it changes shape.
What the fuck? Why is it doing that?
I'm confused.
Whatever. Put it there.
Now we need a table here.
Have a nice big picture there.
Actually, the big picture should be in the big room.
This one seems more sinister so that goes in here in the sinister room.
This is the sinister room.
For sinister people.
And in the sinister room for sinister people, we need the bewitching table.
I wonder if this counts as a table? Hold on, let me...
And then we go here and click there.
This house is missing a light source and a chair.
Oh, it does count as a table! That's amazing!
Let's have a lantern there.
And a chair. Do we have a chair?
Already?
Guess not.
See, here what I want to do now is...
I want to make this a platform as well.
I'm going to make this so accessible.
It's going to be wild.
Yeah, let's make normal ass chairs for now.
That's okay.
There.
This one should be good, right?
This housing is suitable.
That's what I like to see.
Actually, this fits better in here.
And put it one more to the right.
We have this one there.
Where's my chairs?
Oh!
I threw them away somehow.
There we go.
I wonder if this counts.
That could be cool to have.
I could put that. No, I kind of want to keep that actually on me.
Do that.
There.
I'm going to do this now.
Do we have any lamps?
Anything lampy?
Doesn't look like it.
All right, fine.
We're going with this for now.
Not there.
There.
And here.
That's nice.
So this should be good, right?
Did Rosalva just try to move in here?
I hope not.
Housing is suitable. Housing is suitable.
Housing is already occupied.
Motherf- No, no, no. You don't deserve to be here, motherfucker.
You're going to be- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You get to stay there.
That's your fucking room.
This room is missing a wall! Oh! Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Say what now?
Really?
Oh, well, I need the other wall.
Hold on, have it.
Construction, there we go. Oh, that's not a lot though.
Let me make some more.
Ah, fuck, how was it?
How did I make that wall again?
Planked wall.
What was the recipe?
Was it really not just stone and wood?
Are you kidding me?
It is!
Where's my wood?
Did I drop that somewhere?
No, I have wood here.
Stone there.
Oh, do I need maybe another table for that?
Ah!
I see.
Make a bunch there.
Okay, okay, okay.
I see.
Now, is this fine now?
Suitable? Suitable.
Beautiful.
Now, who's moving in?
Why are you here?
Rosalva, I already gave you a home, damn it.
I thought you liked the tree.
Izzy, you motherfucker, you belong in here.
That's your place.
You don't get to have the big room.
No way, remove that.
You're not here.
Fjell?
Nobody's in here yet.
Oh wait, Spaget?
I feel like Spaget belongs up here.
That's your room, Spaget.
Let's have her and keep, yeah.
He hangs out down there, that's fine.
That's cool.
I like his style.
Let's have a Gothic bookcase somewhere.
We have enough of those.
No more Gothic bookcases.
Let's put a zombie banner.
Because why not?
Let's just do it, you know?
Don't even question it.
There.
Weather vane.
Everything's looking nice.
Constellation, we already have one of these, so...
I feel like that's not good.
Alright, I'm gonna sell that.
There you go.
Buy this as well.
Sandstone workbench.
They're sort.
Click this button.
The unpleasant thingy.
I'll put that in here.
What else do I not use?
Let's think.
I do not use...
Wall.
In.
Also the nasty guy here.
I'm not using that.
But hold on, it was a material, so I want to check it.
Handgun was a material, let's check it.
I should sell this.
That one I already checked.
This is not a material.
Sell it.
Alright, Hanno.
Have that one, have that one.
Ooh, one gold!
Sick.
Oi!
Not yet, I need to check with Dylan first.
Phoenix Blaster.
Hellstone... oh, Hellstone Bar.
I need to find myself some of that.
What about this?
These swords are so weird.
Like you combine swords with other swords.
So basically, I need to keep all swords.
Actually, all swords need to be kept.
Alright, this looks good.
I think we are about ready.
Oh, this one.
Dungeon Voss.
Let's have a dungeon... there.
And let's have one... there.
This is the dungeon theme, the rooms.
Oh wait, I can't.
Oh, the clock is blocking that.
There we go.
Alright, everything is reversible.
Now the question is...
Will the NPCs be able to get up here?
Because I didn't make a ladder.
I'm not sure they will be.
Look.
He's supposed to be up here, but he's there.
I'm going to come back later and check.
Close this door, will ya?
Heal.
Quit wasting my time.
Okay, fine.
What's this again?
What did that do?
Wait a minute, what was that?
Sticky dynamite.
Oh, okay.
I guess I can make this.
Why not?
There we go.
Yes.
Now.
This one has that.
Let's bring one of these out.
I have two of these actually.
They're the exact same.
I can sell one of them.
And this goes up here.
Plop.
Okay.
What is my plan now?
I can't believe I didn't find any keys to open those damn chests over here.
What the fuck?
What a crazy place, by the way.
I want to go back here.
But actually,
I needed to check something first.
Potions.
Did I have any more of those
randomly teleportation things?
Otherwise, I want to try and make one.
Organics.
What was it?
There was one specific thing I tested that gave me all kinds of options for potions.
I think this one.
Let's take these for now.
Yeah, let's just test these real quick.
Dylan, you got to remind me here, man.
I'm sorry, I keep asking you.
What do we got?
Increased mana regen, falling speed, aura of light.
Location of enemies.
Soggy, the elder slime has arrived.
Okay.
Hanging day bloom.
When a cosmic ray penetrates a star cloud, that fantastic light.
What the fuck is this?
Okay.
I feel like I should always use this.
Bottled water, day bloom, and iron ore.
Also, can I harvest this now?
Yes, sir.
But I don't get any seeds.
So it's not really sustainable.
I think I'm doing something wrong.
I need to use another item to harvest.
You know, just like Minecraft?
Well, not exactly like Minecraft.
There you have to till the earth, I guess.
So yeah.
This one.
Location of treasure and ore.
Great.
Chance to get a crate, that's actually so nice.
Max number of minions.
This one.
That's actually...
Oh, is this like some really rare fish, prismite?
Fuck, I don't...
The thing I...
I think I really don't like about this crafting system is that...
I wanna craft a bunch of potions,
but I don't wanna go through the process of finding the right materials,
having them all in my inventory,
being next to the bottle,
and then opening and doing it.
I feel like I don't wanna do it.
So I would rather just skip it and not do it,
because it's so much work.
So for now,
put this in here.
Ah, not these.
Like, I wish it would use the items in my chests directly,
instead of having it be in my inventory.
That is just...
crazy to me.
What do we have over here?
Put these in here.
This can be...
Let's say keys.
Although this is one of those things.
You know what? Actually, bring them.
I would probably always wanna have those keys
inside the money trough.
Because when I finally need them,
I don't wanna go all the way back to grab it and then come,
you know? So...
Sort these.
Maybe I don't need six shadow keys though,
but whatever. Ah, not whatever.
Let's put them in here.
One, two, three. We can have one in here.
There we go.
Then we put this weapon in here.
That's not a weapon.
There.
Nice. Alright, let's go.
Adventurer waits.
Soggy!
Edmund, the clothier has arrived.
Hold on a second now.
Wait a minute.
You look exactly
like my accessory.
Where is it?
Here, look!
What the fuck?
Look what I found, man!
I keep having vague memories
of tying up a woman and throwing her
in a dungeon?
Bro.
Is that what brings you happiness?
What's normal anyways?
Bro, what the fuck?
Terraria community.
What?
Reddit?
Ella the mechanic?
Bro, all the people are coming by.
Bro, you sell this for one gold?
To where I younger, I would ask
Katelyn out. I used to be quite the lady killer.
Bro.
What are you going to say next?
Being cursed was lonely.
So I once made a friend out of
leather. I named him Wilson.
You're not making this better.
I'm just going to say you
Edmund.
You...
Thanks again for freeing me from my curse.
Felt like something jumped up and bit me.
Wait, did I free you?
Wait, what have I done?
I don't remember this.
I wonder if...
You are a terrible person.
I wonder if this...
This is definitely him.
I mean...
So this is a voodoo doll of him.
Maybe when I acquired this voodoo doll
that's when he was rescued.
Because someone held a spell over him
by having this voodoo doll.
Mama always said I would make a great tailor.
Really? That's what she said?
I know everything they
is to know about the clothier in business.
Alright, man.
Whatever.
I'll see you around, alright?
Now, didn't someone else just arrive?
Soggy the elder slime. Let's check him out.
Humble grumble.
You get to be pet. There you go.
I'm going inside the house.
Imagine getting an item where you can do this forever.
I would like that.
Probably a bit too OP.
But, you know...
Vultures ain't shit anymore.
Not after I have my crazy-ass items.
Eh!
Maybe it's easier to just walk like this.
Was I ever down here?
I think I was.
Let's just quickly take a look.
Oh yeah, this was the...
Wait, I actually never explored more to the right here.
Let's just do that while we're here.
Yeah, why not?
He looks so silly when I walk around with a balloon.
It really does look like I was
walking around with a balloon.
At a theme park, you know?
Oh, wait!
Ah, I should have brought my...
Oh wait, do I have it?
Ah, damn it.
I should have brought my mining potion.
That would have been crazy. But I'm going to equip this.
That's still okay. I mean, it's going to make it faster.
But we could have been brrrring
if I brought it, you know?
Oh wait, I can't go through that.
Let's go down one.
Oh, wait, there's a chest there.
Ah, I looted it already.
Of course.
That's kind of scary.
Wait, did I die here or something?
Why did I not explore this further?
Ah! Oh, you actually saved my life just now.
What the hell is going on here, bro?
Okay, we're going back to the surface.
Okay. Good to map it out, though.
Map out the world.
Oh, am I not able to?
Okay, I am able to destroy this. Good.
Let's go further down.
Oh, wait, these things.
I do wonder.
Oh, should I try this again?
He drops the samples.
I want to do this again.
Oh, I was ready for that one, bitch.
Nice.
Screams echo around you.
So I think I need to do this three times.
If I remember correctly.
Let me actually prepare a
place to
engage this guy.
Because if I engage this down here, I need to be ready.
I'm going to do this
here.
I'm going to go all the way up here and fight him here.
It's going to be a little tight, though.
Also, I should have brought my potions of defense.
I can't even make a second one, similar to the Skeletron fight.
Maybe this is overkill. Maybe not. Get away!
I'm stuck here. There we go.
Oh, here we go. What? Already?
What's happening? Why is it so quick?
I'm not ready! Get rid of all these.
Oh my god, this is horrible.
Rolly has departed. I don't care about that right now, dude.
It's so dark in here.
I'm going to do the same thing I did last time. I'm going to wait here.
Nice tissue sample.
I'm not going to kill the last thing yet, because I want to heal.
And he's going to engage some sort of Super Saiyan mode soon.
When can I heal? Two seconds.
There we go. Okay. Now I wait a bit longer.
Run!
Dude, this is so good!
Having these platforms here is actually insane.
This is the ultimate strategy.
Just wait a bit here. 30 seconds.
Oh!
Actually, wait. Do I have my... Oh, yeah. Let's just do this.
I can't fire. I don't think I have that, but I do have this.
Let's put this on as well.
Uh...
That seems right.
Okay. Blood moon. Now!
Fuck you!
Bro, this guy is taking a shit ton of damage!
Which one are you? You!
Ah! Just do this.
Which one?
There we go. That's the one.
Yeah, there it is!
Hey, hey! Nice!
Let's see.
Treasure bag.
Cream-tained tissue brain of confusion.
Yeah, I already have this.
Okay, cool. We got some more tissue samples.
That was awesome.
That was smooth, man.
Give me that. Give me the statue.
What is walking around? Is it that fucking thing right there?
Fuck off.
Alright.
Okay, nice!
I'm happy about that.
Let's see.
Oh!
Go away from me.
Now we need...
Nice. Look at this blood water.
It's nasty.
Oh, another one of these.
There's actually stuff below me as well.
Nice.
It's so dark. It's so dark.
Make a little...
Oh, look at that.
I don't need to see shit to play this game.
I can play blind.
Okay.
All of it got spanked by explosives.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Holy fuck, that scared me.
Ooh, that was loud.
Alright, I need to go back immediately because I dropped a shit ton of gold.
And because I'm an idiot,
I didn't have that gold in my money trough.
What is wrong with me?
So that thing was trapped, huh?
Well, well, well.
Now I'm going to be wary of every single chest I find.
Shit.
The game got me good though.
I will say that.
It got me.
Where did I go again?
Oh, it's right there actually.
Ah, just kill them.
I just walked through them, man.
No problems there.
I should have had my potion on to see danger.
That probably would have revealed that shit.
Uh, here?
Tell me my gold is here.
Oh, wait.
No, over here I died. This is where I died.
Uh, here?
Where the fuck is my gold?
Hold on, do I have?
I do.
A meteorite has landed.
No fucking way.
More.
Cool.
Yeah, I got it all back.
Beautiful.
Huh?
Oh, there's a trap.
I see now.
Place the damn torch.
Okay.
Let me also put this on again.
Let's see. Silver, recall.
Aha! Now that's what I want.
I don't want that.
Shoe spikes!
Allows the ability to slide down walls, improved ability if combined with climbing claws.
Oh, neat.
So I guess I can take my climbing claws, combine it with that and make both into one.
That's my prediction on that.
Uh...
I need to summon this.
Okay, drink this.
Summon that. Get in here.
Deposit all. Take the things that I needed.
Such as...
This one possibly.
Uh, Titan.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Delete that.
Taggers also take damage.
Lesser healing? No.
Yes.
Let's actually do that.
In fact...
Do that.
Not that it actually takes them down, but you know.
Whoopsie cushion!
May annoy others. I didn't know I had that.
Cool.
I'm gonna pull some sick pranks.
Oh, oh!
Activates when opened.
Dead man's chest.
Okay.
Put it in.
Why is cobweb considered danger?
Maybe because it slows you down?
What's that?
Oh, I'm also gonna drink this.
Hell yeah.
Whoops. No, that's not what I wanted, but that's fine.
That actually worked out beautifully.
I wanted to put on this.
Ah! Look at that!
There's the button.
Get rid of that.
Just mine all of that.
Okay.
Where should I go? Whoa!
Hold on.
Okay.
No, I want to go back over here.
Maybe I can... I'm gonna dig my way all the way to here.
That's my current objective.
Why you may ask? Because I can.
That's the answer to that.
That's gonna be cool as hell.
Also, I need my glow sticks.
Dig!
Also, put this...
Man, I need a... There.
Go.
Man, this is just pure blood.
Nice.
Oh my god.
Blink root.
I need that mining speed potion, dude.
Wait, what is that? Is that actually gold?
Hold on.
I think it is, but it's...
It's not a lot.
Whoa! My game just...
Are we okay?
My game just slowed down to like three FPS
and no sound for like a couple seconds.
That was weird.
What is that actually?
What is that square there?
I mean it's lead, but there was something behind the lead.
Oh look, we're moving into the blue cave now.
Absolutely love the scarab bombs.
They're so cool.
We've got treasure!
Oh, what's that?
Topaz.
Flaregon.
Honestly, it deleted.
Out of here.
Bro, I'm totally speedrunning this dungeon here.
This is no issue at all for me.
The fuck is that?
Oh!
I thought it was a door, but it's actually a painting, I think.
I'm taking that. Land!
Okay.
Band of Regeneration.
Lead that.
Sure.
I will take...
Night Owl potion. I will actually drink one of those.
Please sort.
Further down.
The faster I go through this, the better too, because...
The potion I have.
Hermes boots.
They work and run super fast.
So that does the same thing that this does, but mine has an extra thing on it, so cool.
Zoom out.
Let's just actually... let's play zoomed out for a bit here.
Just for the sake of treasure.
Another whoopsie cushion.
Oh, I thought that wall was thicker.
That was a bit of a waste.
Oh, no. Now we're in a different biome.
We're making it into that biome over there.
Ancient gold helmet?
Huh.
Straight up armor piece.
That's interesting.
Just do that.
There's a location of enemies. Yeah, you know what? I'm gonna drink that too.
You only live once.
What is... oh, a man-eater.
Oh, that... oh, it's the plant thing.
Right, okay.
Okay, he's... oh, sir.
Calm yourself.
We gotta zoom in a bit more.
Where do we wanna go?
To the right.
Haha.
Hey, what's happening?
Oh, it causes status effects.
What kind of status effects?
Oh, it's making me move weirdly.
I guess I got bit by something.
I like the music here.
Oh, look at this. Oh, wait, I've been there.
This is the place I've been.
And then we have this spot over here, which is super interesting.
Maybe there's a way inside from somewhere over here instead.
So that's what I'm gonna experiment with now.
What am I taking damage from?
Oh, it's you.
I should be careful here.
Wait, fleeting nature skip?
What is that?
6% reduced mana cost plus 2% movement speed?
Hey, that's kinda cool.
It's a material as well.
Gotta ask Dylan about it.
Life crystal? I'll take it.
Oh, it's an enemy, never mind.
I thought it was a treasure.
Like, what the fuck?
Do I want to go down or up?
Nice, just came in handy there.
You know what, actually?
Let's keep going down.
Let's drain the shit out of this place.
Oh, look at the draining!
I love draining!
A star statue?
I wonder if I place this somewhere upstairs.
Will that allow me to spawn more stars?
I mean, coming from the sky, I mean.
Ah, no, no, deposit all.
Shit.
What can I delete here?
Just delete that.
That, that.
I guess this as well, for now.
Delete that!
Is it a material? It's not, so fuck it.
This one can be deleted.
The sand log is gone.
Do these stack? They don't.
Dynamite is gone.
This one is gone.
This one can go.
That one.
There we go. Much better.
Cool?
Oh, we got a little hot!
Wait a minute. Oh, shit.
I should have checked something real quick.
I wanted to see if that was a material.
The flare gun, that is.
I like that candelabra there.
Or chandelier.
So, hold on. Chandelier is when it hangs from the ceiling.
Candelabra is when it stands on a table.
Right?
I think that's true.
Man, this place is huge.
Oh, actually, before I go down,
I need to take a quick look up here.
Because I don't see if there's another way inside of that place.
Ah, look, there it is.
How do we get in?
Let me in!
I need to get inside your special club.
Bro, what are these things?
And why do I take damage from them when I do that?
I take a lot of damage from that as well.
I don't get it.
Jungle spores.
Hold on, let me actually take that.
Looks like there's slimes and crawdads in there.
What are they doing in there?
Also, can I?
Let's try something.
Jungle spores.
More.
Actually, I do want to collect those.
May as well do it.
I'm lazy.
Thank you.
I am excavating all around this little fucking bastion here.
What's up, dude?
Ah, let me in.
Can I really not mine any of this?
That's incredible.
Fuck off.
It's excavating time.
Actually, I'm going to do a quick experiment because I wasn't doing it very thoroughly last time.
Let's go straight up.
No.
It don't work.
I wonder if I can get in there with the random teleportation potion.
In fact, that potion is intriguing me so much.
No, get in there. There we go.
Oh, look at that. I see things in there. What is that?
Oh, that looks exciting.
It's exciting.
There we go.
It looks like we've reached the edge here.
But I'm not done.
I found the perfect technique to mine up.
Basically, you hold the mine button upwards.
You spam jump and you spam the hook.
That way, you just keep going up.
I'm not even looking at the screen.
It's incredible.
That's how you do it.
It looks like we've reached the roof here.
Or whatever you want to call it.
We can't go further up here.
Oh my god.
This is so nice.
I'm stuck.
What's happening?
Oh, no mine. I'm fine.
That's a trap.
There we go.
Give me that.
Okay, so... this way?
No, I can't go further down there.
Not bad.
Stop mining the thing you can't mine.
That smart thing is not very smart often.
What is going on here?
I like the music.
It looks like I'm approaching the point I was at before.
Let me actually go there.
Oh my god.
Stop it.
I'm lazy.
We have made it around.
We got the outline now.
Wait, can I...
Wait, where did it go?
Ah, here.
Oh, no, it's an enemy.
That's a lot of HP, bro.
What's happening down there?
Oh, it's getting hit by my...
I want to see if this thing spawns another one of these things that drop the...
Thing is, you know what I mean.
Actually, I'm going to do this.
Autopause off.
So, what does this say?
It needs...
TE.
Something golden.
Almost the...
Aztec looking symbols.
Sky blue flower.
Oh.
Didn't even see I got that.
Can't bomb it.
Hmm.
I'm so curious about this place, man.
Fuck.
I didn't test on the left side, though.
Okay.
Fuck it. Let's go back.
Need to empty my inventory.
And then I actually want to...
I'm going to go straight down after that.
Like here.
No, let me put... Let me try and place the statue.
Let me see if I'm correct here in my...
Guess.
Put that there.
Maybe it's going to spawn more stars from the sky.
Chandelier.
We can put that somewhere.
That looks nice.
Look at that.
Beautiful.
Ah, jungle torch.
That produces green light, huh?
Meh.
Not right now.
Uh, hold on.
What else did I find?
Silt! Wait a minute!
Was it that one?
I could do something with that.
Hold on.
Wait, was it actually this one? Let's double check.
Extract the nadir. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Placing silt slash fossil piles.
Oh, wait a minute. Maybe I need to...
Alright, Dylan.
Tell me about the silt.
I can make...
stucco?
Uh...
Really? Hold on. There's got to be...
Oh my god.
Guys, I am unhappy
with how that worked.
Because so far in this game,
I've been trying this to no avail.
Clicking on something and using it on something in the world.
Like, except placing objects, of course.
But like this over here,
you right click it,
and it opens a little thing where you put things in.
Otherwise, you open the inventory next to something
and click here, and then something happens.
It seems like there's a whole separate system
for everything in this game. It makes zero fucking sense.
But I'm glad I just discovered that.
The thing is, I'm worried now
that I'm gonna miss so much shit
because of these obscure mechanics.
Fucking hell.
I'm probably gonna miss a ton because of that.
It's not consistent.
That's the thing.
Um, but it's cool that I can do this.
This is actually really nice.
So I can place silt in there and what else?
What does it say?
Slash and fossil piles.
Okay.
Gotcha.
Yeah, I should have kept all my silt.
I threw all that away in the beginning of the game.
Well, it's silt, right?
So why wouldn't you throw it away?
Now, tell me about this.
Blue dye, no surprise there.
But I also got something else, didn't I?
Did I put that in here?
Was it inside of this?
What did I put in here?
Oh yeah, this one.
And...
Actually, take all.
Do that.
And take all.
And do that.
Is this empty now? Put money in?
So we don't forget.
Land.
That's actually a nice looking painting there.
I want that here.
That's nice.
Land.
And...
So here's the thing.
I'm not even going to ask.
Actually, I never mind.
Dylan, just quickly tell me what I already know.
Exactly.
Yep, tiger climbing gear.
What?
Allows the ability to climb walls?
Bro, okay, I was not expecting that.
I was just expecting those two things to go together.
But dude...
Ah, here.
I need to find my climbing thingies.
There.
And then...
Here.
Bam!
Oh, this is also a material.
Oh, whoa, hold on now.
But before we do anything,
I need to test this.
Amazing.
I like that.
And I can do it while falling as well.
Ah, nice. That's actually cool.
Pretty dope, but it takes up a slot where you know it's...
It's nice, but is it really needed?
That's the thing.
Dylan, what can I make with this?
Master ninja gear.
Allows the ability to climb walls and dash.
Gives a chance to dodge attacks?
Wait, are you talking iframes?
Tabi.
Black belt.
Oh my god, how do I get a black belt?
Frog gear.
Grants the ability to swim?
increases jump speed and allows auto-jump.
What is auto-jump?
What does that even mean?
It ain't easy being green.
And frog webbing.
Allows the ability to climb walls.
Jump speed and allows auto-jump.
Fall resistance. Hey, that's pretty cool.
Speaking of fall resistance,
I actually have an item
that eliminates fall resistance
if I'm not mistaken.
Here, negates fall damage.
What could I make with that again?
Remind me, Dylan.
Let's see.
Oh yeah, right, that was the whole balloon thing.
Can I actually make any of these?
Sandstorm and a balloon.
Sharkron balloon.
Honey balloon.
Fort.
Blizzard.
That makes... wait, wait, that makes...
No.
No way.
I can make that right now.
Holy shit.
Yo, that's...
That's amazing.
Wait, what?
Here.
Yeah.
Wait, do I lose anything by doing this?
Is this just a win-win?
I guess I lose 2% melee speed, but who cares?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, increase this jump height.
This one.
Oh, okay, yeah, okay, yeah.
And negates fall damage, bro.
Yo.
Yup.
That's an easy craft.
Now I wonder...
What else can I make with what I have?
Wait.
It's actually just a balloon attached to a horseshoe.
Attached to a lion.
Are you kidding me?
That's insane.
So wait.
No damage.
Incredible.
Dude, that would have saved me
so much during the Skeletron fight,
actually.
Skeletron is...
I died so much from fall damage there,
remember?
Make iron.
Oh, I can only make one?
All right, fine.
Do that.
Let's put the stuff in here.
Pop, pop, pop.
Whoopsie cushion.
Dylan.
He must be so annoyed of me by now.
I keep coming into this house.
Dylan!
Tell me what I can do with this.
What can I make?
Fart in the jar?
Oh, wait.
This is...
I guess this is just another path
to making what I just made, I guess.
Right?
May annoy others.
What can I make with this, Dylan?
Don't fucking leave me.
Yeah, look.
Okay, so I can make the same ones.
So, there's different paths to the same result.
Okay, cool.
That's good to know, I guess.
Um...
Fleeting nature's gift.
What can I do with that?
Mana flower.
Automatically use mana potions when needed.
8% reduced mana cost?
That's not bad.
I mean, that's decent.
I can make it, actually.
And this is also a material.
So yeah, let's do that. Mana potion, I have it.
Mana potion...
In potions, probably.
Thank you.
Actually,
I should get used to just...
Instead of taking all,
just take one.
Because I only need one.
Do I do it down here, Dylan?
Fuck, I gotta ask you again, don't I?
Nope, not that one.
I need...
Tinkera's works. Oh, of course.
Actually, not of course, because it says mana potion.
That's not obvious at all.
Mana flower.
I got it.
Plus 3% movement speed.
That's cool.
Now, Dylan, what can I do with this one?
It's the mana flower. Oh, here we go.
What is this?
Magnet flower.
Increases pickup range for mana stars.
Mana cloak?
Causes stars to fall after taking damage?
Stars restore mana when collected.
What?
That's pretty cool.
But how do I get a star cloak?
Celestial magnet.
Putrid scent.
Enemies are less likely to target you.
I guess that would be great if you're using
a lot of minions.
Right?
Like, have them tank for you?
I kinda wanna make this, because it looks badass.
I wanna be a...
badass sorcerer.
Oh!
Speaking of magic and shit.
There was a potion that increased magic damage
by 20%.
And I forgot what I needed to make it.
That's not good.
That's... Actually, actually.
I have a great idea on how to check
potions from now on.
Just take the bottles, because that will show me
any potion, right?
Hopefully.
I don't need to supply the ingredients.
I can just give them this and be like
dude, tell me.
Maybe not this one. Maybe the water one.
Oh, here we go. Here we go.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Holy water.
Spreads the halo to some blocks?
The fuck is halo?
Spreads corruption?
Spreads the crimson.
Oh!
That's what I need!
Pixie dust?
I need better healing potions.
What else can I make?
This one.
Death wheat, fallen store, moon glow.
I fucking have all that!
Uh, hold on.
Moon glow?
Death wheat?
No, that's not it.
Death... Do I have death wheat?
I must have.
Up here, maybe.
I do.
Lovely.
And then, uh, stars...
Wait.
Gelanius?
Did I put them in here?
Fuck, I don't remember where I put them.
That's so painful.
It's gotta be here though.
Where would I put them?
Are they here?
Bro, I must be blind.
I have...
Up here?
No, no, no, cancel.
Sword.
I had like 150.
I know I have them.
Not this either.
I'm losing my...
Is it up here?
I don't know where the fuck they are!
Bro, I...
I can't find them.
Where the...
What?
I checked every chest.
I'm losing my mind.
Okay.
Nope.
Is it here?
No.
Here?
Let's sort them while we're at it.
It's not in here either.
Oh, I hate this.
Let me search for it.
Here? Here?
Where the fuck?
I think I lost them.
There's no other fucking explanation.
I have no other chests.
I have no fucking clue where they could have gone.
I don't understand what's happening in this game.
Yeah, it's gone.
It's not in here, is it? Randomly?
No clue.
I'm gonna find them in some really stupid place later on.
And I'm gonna feel so stupid.
I just know it.
But for the life of me, I can't figure it out right now.
For all intents and purposes,
I have lost those stars.
They do not exist.
Incredible.
Oh, well.
Put this in here.
And this goes...
Actually, do I even need these anymore?
Kinda useless now.
Unless there's some other obscure thing
I can do with them later, right?
Put them in there.
Uh...
This one is a Michelinius.
Whoopsie cushion.
I have two of them. I may actually just sell one of them.
Ah, no. Keep them.
Dude, I have so many of these!
Sell most.
Sell this too. Sell this too.
And that.
I have two of these. What's the point?
I need to do experiments with that.
So, okay. Oh, actually,
I need to try and equip it and talk to the guy.
Maybe that will do something.
How about that?
Shop.
Buy my things.
Oh!
Savings.
Actually, cool that they show that.
Oh, yeah, look. This one has to be platinum.
I have zero of that. Oh, nice.
Okay.
Let's confirm that at least.
Uh, not...
Did I?
I think I have one left.
Someone, uh,
sell this shit. I don't need it.
Now, this one. I already have one of these.
And it's the same, isn't it?
Yeah.
Sell that.
And I think that's it for now.
Okay.
Uh...
What did I have in here again?
Is it empty? Yeah.
Click this button.
And I think we're about ready to do things.
So, what I want to do now,
I want to
go fish with the potion that I have
that will allow me to find more crates.
And I have that, don't I?
Oh, I thought I had it.
I need to make it then. That's okay.
I can make it that easy.
I have bottled water, I have
bottles as well.
Somewhere.
Don't tell me I put them in here or something.
That would be something I would do.
Fuck!
Where do I leave my bottles now?
Are they up here?
Oh my god!
There they are.
Fuck!
What is wrong with me, man?
Oh, that feels bad.
I knew I was losing my mind.
I fucking knew I had 150 something.
God damn it!
Okay, but now, where's my bottles?
And not these.
I'm talking glass bottles.
I must have put them away as well.
Now I don't know where they are.
They're not in here.
Where did I put them?
In here?
What about here?
Here?
Sort these.
Ah, man.
I feel like I...
See, now I can't find my bottles.
I swear to god, this is just like real life.
I can never find...
When I come home after a day of work,
you know how you take off your hat, your gloves,
your coat and all that,
and you normal people put them in a pile or whatever, right?
Or hang them in the same spot.
For some reason, what I do,
I walk inside, I take off my shoes
and I don't even realize where I put the shoes.
Like, I could put them in the bathroom for whatever reason.
My hat goes on the fucking
table and my gloves
go underneath the computer table for some reason.
Because I'm somewhere else in my mind
and I keep throwing them everywhere.
And then I'm like, what the fuck are my gloves?
This is exactly the same.
It's wild.
I need... this is why I need the game
to guide and hold my hand with this
because I can't handle it.
It's too much for me.
I'm just not equipped
to deal with these situations here.
It's... it's...
There they are!
Found them.
Alright.
Uh...
Finally. Now.
Tell me.
Let's make some potions.
I want to make
this... the star one.
That one.
Deathweed and Moonglow.
Right.
Let's grab that. Let's try that again.
Deathweed.
Moonglow.
And now
the moment we've all been waiting for.
Make them all. Yes!
So now,
when I fight a boss, I'm gonna use this
and I'm gonna fucking wreck.
Because this
is magic damage.
Yep.
Pretty cool.
Okay, now.
Dylan.
Let's make some shit happen here.
I want the block thing.
Sorry, the crate potion.
Where's that?
Hooked fish, mining speed,
Swifty and liquids.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Yes!
Oh, I need a chaos fish.
Oh, I bet you I can
fish that in the blood water.
In the caves.
Fire Blossom, though.
Not sure where I get that.
But okay. Okay.
Precise the luck of the user.
I wish what luck meant.
Where's the, uh...
Throw this to make someone smell terrible?
Appetition...
Why can't I find the one now?
Night vision...
That! There it is.
Oh my god.
No, I used all my munglo.
This is a disadvantage.
Disaster!
So many potions.
That's awesome!
I want to make them all.
Mealy... oh, what is this now?
Mealy and whip attacks.
Have you ever used a whip?
I've used a yo-yo.
Is that the same thing?
I mean, obviously it's not when you think about it all
loud, but maybe in this game it is.
I'm not sure.
It's something on a string, right?
Uh... sure.
Just remember, fallen stars are in ammo.
Ammo!
Good.
Let's put the stuff back.
This one...
is not needed right now.
This one is actually...
pretty cool. I'm gonna put that on...
What just...
Oh, is that a star? I think it was a star.
And potions.
Rest looks good.
Golden keys, city and shield.
Put that on.
Alright!
Let's go digging.
Uh...
Speaking of...
digging.
Let me take some gold.
Let's go to... fjell.
Fjell!
Yes! Gold is stronger than iron.
What are they teaching these humans nowadays?
That's a fucking lie.
Wait, you're not the one I want to talk to.
I need to talk to Mortal, sorry.
Mortal.
Even Dante wants what I'm selling.
Oh yeah?
28 silver for that?
A small explosion that will not destroy tiles.
Uh...
Give me bombs.
I want bombs.
Because we are going to do some crazy shit now.
Put that gold in there.
So here's my plan.
Plan? Down?
Down?
Down!
Here, that's where I'm going.
And you can't stop me.
Going all the way down.
Why is it so dark? Didn't I put torches here?
Maybe I didn't.
Oh, I did sort of, but very haphazardly.
And very irregularly.
Fuck you!
Okay, so we're in this cave now.
Uh...
Yeah.
Maybe it would be more beneficial to go here
and then start from there.
But, no.
You know what? In fact, I'm going to be so lazy.
I'm even going to dig through here.
Right here, actually.
I just want to see what happens if I throw
absolutely all of my bombs.
How far down am I going to get?
There we go.
Hopefully, I didn't hit anything that doesn't explode.
That was probably a bad idea, wasn't it?
Because they explode after a certain time.
That was stupid of me.
Yeah, that was stupid.
But it's okay.
It is what it is.
Uh, please dig.
Oh well, that was a bunch of money wasted.
That's fine.
I'm not mad about that.
Oh, where are we going?
This is actually exciting.
Just digging in the dark.
Dig in the dark.
I don't even want to see where I'm going.
I don't care.
Actually, maybe I do care a little bit.
Where's that potion that allows me to...
I didn't bring it, did I? Fuck.
Oh, I can't get up! I can't see!
There we go.
See, that's why you need light.
You can't just dig without vision.
It's bad.
Also, I need to put on this.
We can dig faster.
Uh-oh.
Oh, that's way too deep for me.
Look at this!
Railway!
Nice!
Get out of here.
Now I'm just going to ride this.
Down, down, down, down.
Oh, here we go.
That's scary.
Okay.
Wait, lava goes into the water and nothing happens there.
Can I go through this?
I can.
Wait, what is that statue?
A tree?
Tree? Well, that spawned trees?
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
Didn't I...
Grant immunity to... I don't think this is fire block.
This is lava.
Um...
I had a potion that granted immunity to this shit, didn't I?
I should have brought that.
I should have thought I had.
Of course that would be lava if you dig deep.
It's okay.
Makes it more exciting.
Another railway. Unless it's the same.
Let me put a torch.
Uh...
I'm just gonna... yeah, down.
I don't want to destroy the railway though.
Get away.
Down we go.
I'm draining the water.
Always exciting.
Oh.
Oof.
Wait, have I been here?
Did I do that? No, I didn't.
I guess this is what happened naturally.
In fact, I should probably take that.
Look, it's naturally gonna make more obsidian.
Down we go.
Did I also have a potion that allowed me to breathe on the water?
I feel like I brought everything that I don't need.
For this expedition. That's just incredible.
I have all these tools here.
And I brought absolutely none of them.
Incredible stuff.
Here we go.
Here we've been.
Ooh.
Ah!
Oh, I'm scared of the lava.
Let's just go down here.
Oh yeah, I'm going down.
Do I have a danger sense thingy?
I don't think I have shit.
I didn't... oh my god.
What is that?
I'll equip this, by the way.
Yeah, I should... bring that.
Yeah.
Also, I think I do want to have this on now.
Let's go to the left.
But the crazy thing is, I can't take fall damage now.
I have to get used to that.
I keep being worried about this.
Oh, there's lava.
Oh, how am I gonna get past this?
Maybe I do need that potion up there, actually.
You know what? Fuck it, we're going home.
I'm gonna grab the necessary things.
I came here unprepared, like an idiot.
Let me fix that.
Quick stack.
Construction.
Still this...
put it in Michelinies.
Bookcase is...
Huh?
There we go. In there.
And in there.
In there.
You know what? Let's try that.
And turn this on.
Let's see if this will make a bunch of trees.
Let's put it...
in a place with no trees.
Here.
Let's check that later, see if there's trees.
It's gonna be exciting.
Okay.
This one...
Let's put it in here.
Lowry is night.
There.
No, not there. This is my...
Speaking of this, I need to...
No, I already did harvest all of that.
Everything's fine.
There.
That looks nice.
And...
potions!
Yes!
What else?
What?
Occasion of enemies? We can take one of those.
So let me not take...
all of them.
Just take one.
Control of gravity.
Mining speed!
Taking two of those.
Danger sense? Yep.
This one is uh...
weird.
I don't know what that means exactly.
Detects hooked fish? What do you mean?
All right. Here we go.
I think we're ready.
There's nothing else I forgot, right?
Let's see.
In fact, you know what? Let's bring...
No, let's not.
We're fine.
Let's go down again.
Have that on.
I wonder if I can have
two of these.
Stack them.
Or four of these.
All four. Imagine that.
I can't take fall damage.
Oh, that feels so wrong to do.
It feels so wrong!
But it feels good.
Oh my god, it's so quick.
Don't fall in lava though.
Uh...
Here.
And here.
Let me kill that guy.
He's annoying me.
Who's that?
Who else wants some?
You want some?
That's right.
That's what you get for being a salamander.
Get through here.
Give me that.
Oh! Oh wait, this is fine.
Uh, are you throwing something, sir?
Oh, here we are.
This is what we were.
Uh...
Danger sense.
Obsidian immunity to lava.
Let's try that.
How long does it last?
Six minutes?
Hey!
Let's also do mining potion. We're gonna go nuts now.
Bombs!
Ha ha ha!
Straight down!
Hurry!
Lava!
Oh my god, where are we going?
Okay, right, we're immune.
Just keep going down.
Oh my god, I have a bad feeling about this.
Oh, what is that?
That looks evil.
In fact, let me guide the lava away
for future me.
That's a genius idea.
Why can't I?
Come on.
There we go.
Guide it away.
I'm gonna make a little, uh...
I'm gonna guide it down here.
I'll guide it to the left.
Look at that!
Future me is not gonna have lava issues.
That shit's gonna go away.
Beautiful.
You can even see the lava moving on the map.
There's also lava here that makes me unhappy.
Get it out of there!
I'm very unhappy.
Now I'm happy again.
Nice.
This lava right here can also fuck off.
And when that lava is gone,
we go straight down.
Oh, here we go. Let me also get rid of this lava while we're at it.
I love guiding lava!
Come on. All of it.
Away you go.
This one is infinite, it seems, somehow.
I don't like that. Let's block that.
Yeah, that makes no sense.
What just happened there, but that's fine.
Whatever.
Then do this.
Uh...
Beautiful. Look at this.
It's clean.
Okay.
What the heck are we...
Look at the background.
Mine tracks here.
I just want to explore this place a little bit.
No, no, no, no, no, no. We stick to the plan.
Straight down.
Don't get distracted.
We go straight down.
I'm going to stick to my goddamn plan.
Oh, here we go. Good thing I put a torch.
Let me see what's coming.
Bombs! Nice.
Oh!
Look at the background.
A demon!
Holy shit, what the fuck is that?
I don't like how that looks.
Shoot it!
I still have lava protection.
Not for long though.
Block that shit.
Get out of here.
Okay, we've got a demon.
Whoa! Shooting something.
Ooh, that's a lot of damage.
It's getting hot in here.
Uh, just do something here.
Block it off.
How do I stop this?
Flow away.
Hellbats?
I am hyper focused right now.
No!
There we go.
Heal.
Can I stand on this?
Okay, I can.
What the fuck? Where am I?
Oh, what the hell?
I need to...
In the moon!
Don't shoot that shit at me.
He dropped something.
Superior demon scythe.
Dude, this is truly the bottom it seems.
49 casts a demon scythe.
Let's try that.
Oh, it's the same thing it did.
It costs a lot of mana though.
Let's try.
Okay.
Eh.
Kinda sucks.
Is it even a material?
It's not.
Okay, I'm gonna have to try that at some other time.
Uh, from now...
Uh, wait, wait, wait.
Summon this first.
Put the money in.
Quick stack.
Delete some ash.
Delete... no, don't delete the self, you motherfucker.
Deposit all.
Let's see here.
Maybe I should drink another one of these just to be safe.
Let's take... let's put this on.
Let's drink this.
Attackers also take damage.
Sure. Sticky bomb. Let's have it.
Actually, I want this in my... there.
There we go.
Look the homing of it!
Absolutely amazing.
Okay, where do I go?
Oh, we're safe.
Oh!
Oh, these are houses!
Obsidian lamp.
Hellfire arrow!
Are we finally gonna get Hellfire bars?
Or was it Hellstone? I forgot.
Obsidian chair, man.
We're gonna make a demon ass room.
Obsidian sofa?
Man, these demons know how to chill.
Oh, they... whoa! They dropped lava!
Good thing I had my potion on!
Lost hopes of man banner?
You know what? Let's just leave that there.
I feel like that may be beneficial to me.
To leave that there.
What the heck, man?
Okay. What's that?
Obsidian candle.
Let me actually try my gun now.
That I have this buff on.
108.
Get shot at!
Oh, he's shooting those!
They have a slow acceleration, but...
They will accelerate.
And fuck you up, it seems.
Let me just zoom in a bit.
How much does that do?
Hellfire arrow.
13.
That's nice.
I don't want to open that door!
It seems like a bad door to open.
What's up, dude?
Let me invade your house.
Nice cream paper you have there.
I'm taking it. It belongs to me now.
What do you want?
Okay, you're actually kind of scary.
Ha ha!
Amazing.
Agile demon scythe.
Man, these things just drop fucking demon scythe, huh?
That's like the thing here.
Give me these.
Man, these don't provide much light, huh?
It's demonic light.
It's not the light we want.
Darkness!
Wait, was that just a frame with nothing in it?
That's what that looked like.
So who the f-
They have architecture and shit down here.
Oh my god.
Oh!
We're fine. We have the potion on.
Hellstone brick.
Material.
Oh, you!
Fire imp.
The classic. Always the imps.
Is this guy carrying...
voodoo demon?
I thought he was carrying a bomb.
Actually, maybe it is a bomb.
What is that?
Hellforge!
I think that's important.
Potion of return.
Teleport you home and create some...
Oh!
Yes!
Yes, dude!
Uh, here?
What's that?
Mushroom torch.
Here's the thing though.
It's late.
I need to stop!
Otherwise I know myself. I'm gonna keep going forever.
Especially now.
Yeah.
It's gotta be the end.
I'm sorry I had to end it on something that exciting,
but I mean, I know
if I didn't stop now, I would just keep going forever
and that's not good.
Other things to do?
Ha ha ha!
That was fun, man!
That was really fun!
I love that.
Uh, let's see here.
I all do one.
Ghost hybrids!
Our local pilot!
Has gifted 10 memberships.
Holy shit, man!
Thank you so much!
I wonder who got them all.
Ghost hybrids.
It's been here since the very beginning.
Since the out-of-wild days.
So nice of you, man. Thank you so much, ghost hybrid.
I don't know if you're still here.
But thank you.
Demon confirmed!
Ha ha ha!
Indeed.
Oh, look at all the stars!
Wait, what's with the stars?
Oh, wait, are you talking...
Oh, it's probably because...
I know what it is. Never mind.
Okay.
Yup!
A star in a bottle!
And literal demon!
First time seeing your stuff. Pretty good.
Hey, Mikey the Great! I appreciate it.
I'm glad you liked it.
I saw you in the beginning, too.
You've been here for the whole stream, then.
That's cool. I'm glad you liked it so much to stay around.
The stars were inside him all along.
It says Vivian.
So star, Oliver.
Awesome.
Hi, Oliver. You made my day with your stream.
Hey, that's awesome, Kratos.
Are you one of the ones who got the membership?
Actually, no.
No, no, no. I've seen you before, haven't I?
You've been a member before this.
Best part of the year.
Asking chat to help with C++
and them actually replying.
That's my chat.
That's my chat!
I got one membership.
Was really surprised to see myself as a straight line
when I came back to look at chat.
I like that phrasing there.
That's cool.
Lost these?
Oh, man. How frustrated were you
when I couldn't see the stars?
I could have...
Oh, I can just imagine the chat
in that moment.
I'm so sorry
for making you suffer.
Oh, man.
I felt proper stupid.
You know what I was thinking, by the way?
Because I couldn't find the stars,
in my mind I was like, okay, you know what?
This magic wand that I used earlier
that at some point didn't work anymore?
Maybe it used the stars
as a...
as a type of ammo and I didn't realize it at the time
and then I just used all of them.
That's what I thought.
But then I could use it again
so I was super confused.
Are you hydrated? I am hydrated.
Thank you. Yes, I am.
Chat was so relieved
when you combined the lucky horseshoe
with your cloud in a balloon.
Really?
Amazing.
Whoopsie cushion.
We're used to it by now?
Ah, that's good.
Or maybe it's not, I don't know.
I was searching with you, lol.
Forgot it's an ammo too. Right?
I didn't even think to look there.
Okay, so when round two?
What do you mean round two?
Do you mean round eight?
This is stream number seven
in the Terraria series.
Or maybe you're making a joke here
that I'm not getting.
Have you played Shadow of the Colossus before?
No, I haven't. Quasi manipulation.
It's on my list of games to play.
I'm excited to play it.
Have you ever considered playing
Gorbinos Quest?
It has like 500 hours of
mind-pumping action?
Really? 500 you say?
That's a bold statement.
I'm gonna add it to the list
to check out later.
Gorbinos Quest.
By the way,
people, I've realized that
you're suggesting a lot of games.
I'm not saying this is one of them,
but a lot of games that are still in early access.
I don't really play early access games
until they're finished, because I don't want to
rob myself of an inferior experience
when I can wait and get the full one.
So if you're about to suggest
something at some point that is early access
or not finished, I'm probably not gonna play it.
So...
It's not a real game?
Oliver, do you actually have ADHD?
Yes, no, no comment.
Um...
The answer is I don't know.
During my Subnautica playthrough,
people pointed out that I may have it.
And maybe I do, who knows.
But then I went to my doctor and I
asked him.
So, I may have ADHD. Can you test me?
And it's not something you do
overnight. So, you know,
he asked me a bunch of questions. He gave me a questionnaire
that I filled out.
We had some talks. He asked me
and we talked some more over different sessions.
And at the end, he was like,
he was unsure, you know?
He wasn't quite
convinced that I had it, but he said,
if it's not interfering in your life, then it's not worth
pursuing anymore.
But the thing is, I don't know.
Who the fuck knows?
Maybe I do have it.
A lot of people do.
It's very possible.
Look at all the people
asking for Neuter, Oliver.
News of PE.
Yeah, I'm excited. It was actually a
toss-up between Neuter and Terraria.
When I was deciding what
game to play next on the stream.
I'm
excited about Neuter
because I've heard so many people speak highly
of it.
I have not
played Team Fortress 2. Axial responsibilities.
But I know what it is.
And I know what it is because I've seen
so much background
footage of it, watching
Valve news network.
Doesn't really matter to be fair.
No, that's gonna be painful.
Yeah, probably.
There's so many good games
to play in so little time, and there's also
just so many other things I want to do.
I feel like I just don't have enough time for
everything nowadays.
What is your favorite NPC
in this game?
Uh...
Hmm...
It's gotta be Dylan.
He's a real G.
Definitely Dylan.
Do I actually think it's a
whoopsie cushion? No, no, it's called
uh...
Hold on. What is it actually called?
Isn't it a
fart cushion or something?
That
I know that's not the name
but there's a name for that.
Fart Cushion.
I don't know.
Maxwell moment?
Dylan is who?
Wait, did I... hold on.
Did I not... did I get his name wrong?
Is he not called Dylan?
We had Maxwell, Joe, and Dylan.
But Maxwell is gone.
Joe is gone.
Dylan is the real G.
It's called Dylan.
Never forget Maxwell and Joe.
I will never forget Maxwell and Joe.
Maxwell defended me
in the very first minutes
of the game.
Where I was but a wee lad
unable to
fend for myself.
And he rescued me.
And I will forever be
grateful and in his debt.
So, yeah.
It really is a blind playthrough.
Guess it is.
Dylan is a backseater.
Feels like my messages are being filtered
even though I know they aren't. Maybe that's on me.
YouTube has a weird system.
I don't actually have anything on top of YouTube.
If anything, it's just YouTube right now.
I had stream elements 1
to do some modding ones, but
I got rid of that.
So, there's nothing I can do about that.
Yeah. Actually, there is.
I can technically green light all of you
so you can send all of it, but that would take forever.
Okay, guys.
This has been freaking amazing.
I'm having the time of my life with this.
This is so cool.
And especially now, I'm excited for the next time.
Especially where I just got.
I should have just gone down in the beginning, man.
Just go down.
So yeah, I'm looking forward to the next stream.
I will see you guys around.
Have a great one, okay?
And enjoy your Saturday.
Goodbye.